clocks let's let's get started so I know lecture today a little bit of a break so
시계의이의 나는 그래서 오늘은 휴식 약간의 강의를 알 수 있도록 시작하자하자
today we're the last time we talked about sort of we saw all the parts of
오늘 우리는 우리가 얘기 마지막 시간은 약 종류의 우리의 모든 부분을보고있어
comments we put everything together today we're going to see some
의견은 우리가 일부를 볼거야 함께 오늘 모든 것을 넣어
applications of contacts
연락처 응용 프로그램
aspect actually dive inside images and talk about spatial localization and
측면은 실제로 이미지 안에 다이빙과 공간 지역화에 대해 이야기하고
detection we were we actually moved this lecture up a little bit we had it later
검출 우리는 우리가 실제로 우리가 나중에 있었다 조금이 강의를 이동했다
on the schedule we saw a lot of guys were interested in this type of projects
일정에 우리는 많은 남자들이 프로젝트의이 유형에 관심 보았다
who wanted to move it earlier to kind of give you an idea of what's what's
무엇 무엇을 누가 종류의 당신의 아이디어를 제공하기 위해 이전으로 이동하고 싶었다
feasible so first couple administrative things are the project proposals were
가능 그래서 처음 몇 행정 가지 프로젝트 제안했다입니다
doing Saturday my inbox kind of exploded over the weekend so I think most of you
토요일에 일을 내받은 편지함의 종류 그래서 당신의 대부분을 생각 주말에 폭발
submit it but if you didn't you should probably get on that we're in the
제출하지만 당신은 당신이 아마에 가야하지 않은 경우 우리는에 걸
process of looking through those will go to make sure that the project proposals
그 통해 보는 과정이 반드시 프로젝트 제안서 있는지 확인로 이동합니다
are reasonable never once admitted one so we'll hopefully get back to you on
한 번에 하나를 합리적으로 인정되지 않습니다 그래서 우리는 희망에 드리도록하겠습니다
your projects this week also home or two is due on Friday so who's who's done who
프로젝트 이번주는 집 또는 두 개의 그래서 사람들이 끝났다 누가 금요일에 의한 사람
stuck on patch norm
패치 규범에 붙어
okay good good that's fewer hands then we saw last week so we're making
우리가 만들고 있어요, 그래서 다음 적은 수의 손을의 좋은 좋은 괜찮 우리는 지난 주에보고
progress also keep in mind that we're asking you to actually trained a pretty
진행은 또한 우리가 당신을 요구하고 있음을 알아 두셔야에 실제로 꽤 훈련
big continent on C far for this homework so if you're starting to train on
지금까지이 숙제 C에 큰 대륙 당신이 훈련을 시작하고, 그래서 만약
Thursday night that might be top so maybe start early on that last part also
상단 될 수 목요일 밤은 그래서 어쩌면 또한 마지막 부분에 일찍 시작
homework 1 were in the process of creating hopefully we'll have those back
숙제 하나는 만드는 과정에 있었다 잘하면 우리는 다시 사람들을해야합니다
to this week you can get feedback before homework to do also keep in mind though
이번 주에 당신은 또한 비록 염두에 두어야 할 수있는 숙제 전에 피드백을 얻을 수 있습니다
we actually have a in class midterm next week on Wednesday so that's a week from
그 일주일에서, 그래서 우리는 실제로 수요일에 다음 주 수업 중간에이
Wednesday so be ready in class should be a lot of fun
수요일 그래서 재미를 많이해야합니다 클래스의 준비
alright so last lecture we were talking about competition that works we can
확실히 우리가 경쟁에 대해 얘기했다 그래서 마지막 강의는 우리가 할 일
absolve the pieces we spent a long time understanding how this convolution
조각을 면제 우리는 어떻게 회선을 이해하는 데 시간이 오래 소요
operator works how we're sort of transforming feature maps from one to
운영자는 우리는 종류의 하나에서 기능지도를 변환하는 방법을 작동
another by running into products over by sliding this window over the map
지도를 통해이 창을 밀어 제품에 이상 실행하여 다른
computing products and actually transforming our representation through
제품을 계산하고 실제로 통해 표현을 변환
many layers of processing and if you remember if you remember these lower
많은 처리 레이어와 이러한 낮은 기억한다면 당신이 기억하는 경우
layers of convolutions tent wherein things like edges and colors and higher
회선 텐트 층, 상기 가장자리와 색상과 높은 같은 것들
layers tend to learn more complex object parts we talked about pulling which is
레이어는 우리가 어떤 당기는 이야기 더 복잡한 객체 부분을 학습하는 경향이
used to some sample and downsize our feature representations inside networks
일부 샘플에 사용되는 네트워크 안에 우리의 기능 표현을 소형화
that's a common ingredient we saw we also did case studies on particular
그것은 우리가 우리는 또한 특정에 대한 사례 연구를했다 보았다 일반적인 성분이다
content architectures you could see how these things tend to get hooked up in
콘텐츠 아키텍처는 이러한 일이에 푹 얻을하는 경향이 방법을 볼 수 있었다
practice so we talk about one at which is something from 98 it's a little fiber
조금 섬유의되는 98 일이 우리가 약을 이야기 그래서 연습
content that was used four digit recognition we talked about Alex not the
우리는 알렉스에 대해 이야기 4 자리 인식하지를 사용 내용
kind of kicked off the big deep deep learning boom in 2012 by winning image
종류의 이미지를 승리로 2012 년 큰 깊은 깊은 학습 붐 시작했다
not come that we talked about ZF that one image net classification in 2013 was
우리는 2013 년 하나의 이미지 그물 분류했다 ZF에 대해 이야기하는 것이 오지
pretty similar to Alex now and then we saw that deeper is often better for
알렉스 꽤 유사한 지금 우리는 깊이가 종종 더 나은 것을보고
classification we looked at Google Matt and PGG that did really well in 2014
분류 우리는 2014 년에 정말 잘했던 구글 매트와 PGG 보았다
competitions that were much much deeper than Alex Natanz and a lot better and we
훨씬 알렉스 나탄 즈보다 더 깊고 더 많이 우리 있었다 대회
also saw this new fancy crazy thing for Microsoft called the ResNet that one
또한 마이크로 소프트는이 새로운 멋진 미친 것은 그 하나 ResNet라고 보았다
just in december in 2015 with hundred and fifty where architecture and as your
그냥 백 오십 곳 아키텍처 등 2015 년 12 월에서 당신의
caller just over the last couple years these different architectures have been
발신자는 지난 몇 년 동안 서로 다른 아키텍처왔다
getting deeper and getting a lot better but this is just for classification so
깊은 점점 더 많아지고 있지만 그렇게 분류 그냥
now in this lecture we're going to talk about localisation and detection which
지금이 강의에서 우리는 현지화 및 검출에 대해 이야기 할 것중인
is actually another really big important problem in computer vision and this idea
컴퓨터 비전 및이 아이디어에 또 다른 정말 큰 중요한 문제는 실제로
of deeper networks doing better chance that all kind of will revisit that a lot
더 나은 기회를하고 깊은 네트워크의 모든 종류의 많은 것을 방문 것이다
in these new attacks as well so so far in the class we've really been talking
이러한 새로운 공격뿐만 아니라 그래서 지금까지 수업 시간에 우리가 정말 얘기를했습니다
about classification which is sort of given an image we want to classify which
종류의 이미지를 부여 분류에 대해 우리는 분류 할
are some number object categories it is that's not nice basic problem in
몇 개의 개체 범주는 그것은 그에서 좋은 기본적인 문제가되지 것입니다
computer vision that we've using that were using to understand comments and
우리가 그것을 사용하여 한 컴퓨터 비전 의견을 이해하기 위해 사용하고,
such but there's actually a lot of other tasks that people were coming to
이러한하지만 사람들이오고 있었다 다른 작업을 많이 실제로있다
so some of these are classification and localisation now instead of just
그래서 이들 중 일부는 분류 및 현지화 지금 대신이다
classifying an edge as well as some category labels we also want to drop
우리는 또한 드롭 할 가장자리뿐만 아니라 어떤 종류의 라벨을 분류
down box in the image to say where that class occurs
클래스가 발생하는 경우 이미지 다운 상자가 대답
another problem people work on its detection so here there's again some
또 다른 문제 사람들은 그래서 여기에 다시 몇 가지 거기의 탐지 작업
pics number of object categories but we actually want to find all instances of
사진 개체의 범주 수 있지만 실제로의 모든 인스턴스를 찾으려면
those categories inside the image and Dropbox around them another more recent
또 다른 최근의 주변 이미지와 드롭 박스 안에 해당 카테고리
task but people have started to work on a bit as this crazy thing called instant
이 미친 것은 즉시 호출로 작업하지만 사람들은 비트에서 작동하기 시작했다
segmentation where again you want you have some pics number about two
당신은 당신이 두 가지에 대한 일부 사진 번호가 원하는 다시 분할
categories you want to find all instances of those categories your image
카테고리는 해당 카테고리의 모든 인스턴스에게 이미지를 찾으려면
but instead of using a box you actually want to draw little contour around and
대신 상자를 사용하는 당신이 실제로 주위에 약간의 윤곽을 그릴 싶어
identify all the pixels
모든 화소를 식별
belonging to each instance instance segmentations kind of crazy so we're not
우리가 아니에요, 그래서 미친의 각 인스턴스 인스턴스 세분화 종류에 속하는
going to talk about that today just thought you should be aware of it and
에 대해 이야기 할 것 오늘은 당신이 그것을 알고 있어야합니다 생각
we're gonna really focus on this these localisation and detection tasks today
우리는 이러한 현지화 및 탐지 작업 오늘이에 초점을 정말거야
and the big difference between these is the number of objects that were finding
이들 사이에 큰 차이가 발견 된 개체의 수이다
so and localisation there's sort of one object or in general effects number of
그래서 및 현지화 하나의 개체 또는 일반 효과 번호 종류가있다
objects whereas in detection we might have multiple objects or a variable
검출에 우리는 여러 개체 또는 변수가있을 수 있습니다 반면 객체
number of objects and this seems like a small difference but it'll turn out to
객체의 수와이 작은 차이처럼 보이지만 그것은을 끌 것
actually make a big
실제로 큰을
be pretty important for architectures so we're gonna first talked about
그래서 우리는 첫 번째에 대한 이야기​​거야 아키텍처에 매우 중요
classification and localisation cuz its kind of the simplest so just to recap
간단한의 종류 사촌 분류 및 현지화 그래​​서 그냥 요약하자면
what I just sad
내가 그냥 슬픈
classification one image to a category label localisation is image to a box and
카테고리 라벨 현지화로 분류 하나의 이미지가 상자에 이미지와
classification localisation means we're gonna do both the same time just to give
분류 현지화는 우리가주는거야 동시에 둘을 의미합니다
you an idea of the kinds of dance that people use for this we talked we've
당신은 사람들이 사용 댄스의 종류의 아이디어는 우리가했습니다 이야기
talked about the image that classification challenge image not also
이미지가 분류 도전 이미지에 대해 얘기하지도
has run a classification + localisation challenge so here
그래서 여기에 분류 + 현지화 도전을 실행하고있다
similar to the classification task there's a thousand classes and each
분류 작업과 유사한 천 클래스와 각있다
training instance in those classes actually has one class and several
해당 클래스의 인스턴스를 훈련하는 것은 실제로는 하나의 클래스 여러가
bounding boxes for that class inside the image and now a test tinier algorithm
이제 이미지 내부 클래스와 테스트 tinier 알고리즘에 대한 경계 상자
organics bypasses where instead of your guesses just being class labels it's a
유기물은 어디 대신 추측 단지 인 클래스 레이블 그것의 우회
class label together with the bounding box and to get it right you need to get
클래스 레이블 함께 경계 상자와 그것이 바로 당신이 얻을 필요가 얻을
the class label rights and the bounding box rights we're getting a bounding box
클래스 레이블 권리와 경계 상자 권한을 우리는 경계 상자가 있어요
right just means you're close in some thing called intersection of
바로 당신이 교차라는 어떤 일에 가까이있어 의미
that you don't need to care about too much right now so again you get it for
그렇게 다시 너무 많은 지금은 걱정하지 않아도 당신은 그것을 얻을
image that at least you get it right if you one of your 5 gases is correct and
이미지 적어도 당신이 당신의 5 가스 중 하나가 올바른지 바로 경우를 얻을 수 있고
this is kind of the main dataset people work on for classification +
이 + 분류에 일 주요 데이터 집합 사람들의 종류
localisation so one really fundamental paradigm it's really useful when
현지화 하나의 정말 근본적인 패러다임 있도록 때 정말 유용
thinking about localisation is this idea of regression so I don't know if
회귀의이 아이디어는 내가 알고하지 않습니다 현지화에 관한 생각
thinking back to a machine learning class you kind of saw like
당신이 가지처럼 보았다 기계 학습 클래스에 다시 생각
classification and regression may be with me regression or something fancier
분류 및 회귀 나 회귀 또는 애호가 뭔가를 할 수있다
and when we're talking about localisation it's really implies we can
우리는 지역화에 대해 이야기 할 때 그것은 정말 우리는 할 수 있습니다 의미있어
really just frame this as a regression problem where we have an image that's
정말 우리의 이미지가 회귀 문제로이 프레임
coming in that image is going to go through some some processing and/or
해당 이미지에 오는 어떤 어떤 처리를 통해 갈 및 / 또는
eventually going to produce for real-valued numbers that promote rise
결국 상승을 촉진 실수 번호를 생성하는 것
this box there's different parameterizations people use common is
이 상자는 다른 매개 변수화 사람들이 일반적으로는 사용할 수있다
XY coordinates of the upper left hand corner and the width and height of the
XY 상부 좌측 코너의 폭 및 높이 좌표
box but you'll see some other variants as well but always four numbers for
상자하지만 당신은뿐만 아니라 다른 변형을 볼 수 있지만 항상 네 개의 숫자에 대한 것
bounding box and then there's some ground truth bounding box which again is
상자를 경계하고 다시 일부 지상 진실 경계 상자가있다
just four numbers and now we have we can compute a loss like maybe Euclidean
단지 네 개의 숫자와 지금 우리는 우리가 아마 유클리드와 같은 손실을 계산할 수있다
losses a pretty pretty standard choice between the numbers that we produced in
손실 우리가 생산 숫자 사이에 꽤 예쁜 표준 선택
the correct numbers and now we can just turn this thing just like we did our
우리가했던 것처럼 정확한 숫자는 지금 우리는 단지이 일을 설정할 수 있습니다 우리의
classification networks where we sample so many batch of data with some ground
우리는 약간의 땅과 데이터의 많은 배치를 샘플링 분류 네트워크
truth boxes we propagate forward computer lost between our predictions
진실의 상자 우리는 앞으로 전파 컴퓨터는 우리의 예측 사이에 손실
and the correct predictions back propagate and just update the network so
올바른 예측은 다시 전파 너무 네트워크를 업데이트
this paradigm is is really easy that's actually makes this localization task
인이 패러다임은 실제로의이 현지화 작업을 만드는 정말 쉽습니다
actually pretty easy to implement so here's a really simple recipe for how
그래서 여기에 구현하기가 꽤 쉬운 방법에 대한 정말 간단한 조리법이다
you could implement classification + localisation so first you just download
먼저 그냥 다운로드 있도록 분류 + 현지화를 구현할 수
some existing preteen model are you train yourself if you're ambitious
당신이 야심 찬 있다면 어떤 기존의 초반 이었죠 모델은 당신 자신을 훈련하는
something like Alex Knight BGG Google met all these things we talked about
알렉스 기사 BGG 구글과 같은 일이 우리가 이야기 모든 것을 충족
last lecture now we're going to take those fully connected layers that were
마지막 강의는 지금 우리가했다 그 완전히 연결 층을거야
producing our class scores were gonna set those aside for the moment and we're
거 우리의 수준의 점수를했다 생성하는 순간 옆 사람들을 설정하고 우리는있어
gonna attach a couple new fully connected layers to some point in the
야는 어느 시점에 몇 가지 새로운 완전히 연결 층을 부착
network this will be called call this a regression had but I mean it's basically
이 회귀가 가진이 호출됩니다 전화 네트워크 그러나 나는 기본적으로 뜻
the same thing as a couple fully connected layers and then I'll puts some
같은 몇 완전히 연결 층과 같은 것은하고는 좀을두고 있습니다
real valued numbers now we train this thing just like we train our
우리가 훈련처럼 실제 값 숫자는 지금 우리가이 일을 훈련 우리
classification network the only difference is that now instead of class
분류 네트워크는 유일한 차이는 현재 클래스의 대신
wars
전쟁
and graduate classes we use Lt loss and crown jewel boxes of Matt we train this
대학원 수업은 우리가이 훈련 매트의 중위 손실과 왕관 보석 상자를 사용하여
network exactly the same way now it s time we just use both heads to do
네트워크 정확히 같은 방법은 지금은 우리가 할 모두 머리를 사용하는 시간이야
classification and localisation we have an image we've changed the
분류 및 현지화 우리는 이미지가 우리가 변경 한 한
classification has we train delocalization heads we pass it through
분류 우리는 우리가 그것을 통과 비편 재화 머리를 양성하고있다
we get class course we get boxes and when we're done like really that's all
우리는 우리가 상자를 수업 과정을 얻을받을 우리가 정말 좋아 완료되면 그게 다야
you need to do so this is kind of a really nice simple recipe that you guys
당신은 그래서 이것은 정말 좋은 간단한 조리법의 종류 할 필요가 너희들
could use for classification + localisation on your projects so other
그래서 다른 프로젝트에 분류 + 현지화에 사용할 수
one slight detail with this approach there's sort of two main ways that
이 방법의 하나 약간의 세부 사항은 두 가지 방법의 종류가 있음
people do this regression task you could imagine a class agnostic regresar or
사람들이 당신이 클래스에 얽매이지 regresar을 상상할 수있는이 회귀 작업을하거나
class-specific regresar you could imagine that no matter what class I'm
클래스 별 당신 regresar 상관없이 클래스 난 없다는 것을 상상할 수
going to use the same architecture the same weights in those fully connected
이들에 동일한 가중치가 완전히 동일한 접속 구조를 사용하는 것
layers to produce my bounding box that would be in your sort of outputting
레이어를 출력하여 정렬에있을 것입니다 내 경계 상자를 생산하는
always four numbers which are just the box no matter the class I'm an
그냥 상자가 더 내가이야 클래스를 상관 없습니다 항상 네 개의 숫자
alternative you'll see sometimes it's class-specific regression we're now
당신이 볼 대안은 때때로 우리가 지금이야 클래스 고유의 회귀이다
you're gonna put see times for numbers that's sort of like one bounding box per
넌 넣어 일종의 당 하나의 경계 상자처럼 번호를 시간을 볼 수있어
class and different people have found that sometimes these work better and
클래스와 다른 사람들이 때때로이 더 잘 작동하는지 발견하고
different cases but it i mean intuitively it kind of makes sense that
다른 경우가 있지만, 나는 직관적으로 의미가 가지 의미가 있습니다 그
something that the way you might think about localizing a cat could be a little
방법은 당신이 조금 될 수있는 고양이 현지화에 대한 생각 뭔가
bit different than the way you localize are trained so maybe you wanna have
당신이 지역화 방법과 다른 비트는 어쩌면 싶어이 그렇게 훈련
different parts of your network that are responsible for those things but it's
그것의 것들하지만 대한 책임은 네트워크의 다른 부분
it's pretty easy venue just it changes your back the way you came to Los a
그것은 꽤 쉬운 장소는 당신의 다시 로스 (A)에 제공된 방법을 변경하는 것
little bit you compute loss only using the ground truth class
조금 만 그라운드 진실 클래스를 사용하여 손실을 계산할
the box for the ground truth class but even that still basically the same idea
지상 진실 클래스의 상자하지만 심지어 여전히 기본적으로 같은 생각
and other design choice here is where exactly you attach the regression had
정확히 회귀가 있었다 부착 위치와 여기에 다른 디자인 선택이다
again this isn't too important different people if you'll see different people do
당신은 다른 사람들이 어떻게 볼 경우 다시는 다른 사람들이 너무 중요하지 않습니다
it in different ways some common choices would be to attach it right after the
그것은 다른 방법으로 몇 가지 일반적인 선택은 바로 후를 연결하는 것입니다
fall of the last convolutional air just sort of mean like you're really serious
당신이 정말로 심각한처럼 마지막 길쌈 공기의 가을은 일종의 의미
initializing new fully connected layers will see things like over feet and BG
새로운 완전히 연결 층을 초기화하는 다리와 BG를 통해 같은 것들을 볼 수 있습니다
localisation work this way another common choice is to just attach your
현지화 작업 또 다른 일반적인 선택이 바로 연결하는 것입니다 이런 식으로 당신의
aggression had actually after the last fully connected layers from the
침략은에서 마지막 완전히 연결 층 후 실제로 있었다
classification of work and you'll see some other things like depots on our CNN
당신이 우리의 CNN에 창고처럼 다른 것을 볼 수 있습니다 작업의 분류
kind of work in this labor but either one works fine
이 노동 작업의 종류하지만 둘 중 하나는 잘 작동
you could attach to just about anywhere and do something so as an aside this is
당신이이 따로 그래서으로 막 어디서나 연결하고 뭔가를 할 수
we can actually generalize this framework to localizing more than one
우리는 실제로 하나 이상의 현지화에이 프레임 워크를 일반화 할 수 있습니다
object so normally with this classification localisation task that we
이 분류 현지화 작업과 그래서 일반적으로 개체가 우리
sort of set up an image that we care about producing exactly one object
일종의 우리가 정확히 하나의 객체를 생성하는 신경 이미지를 설정
bounding box for the input image but in some cases you might know ahead of time
입력 이미지 상자를 경계하지만, 경우에 당신은 미리 알고 있습니다
that you always want to localize some fixed number of objects so here this is
당신은 항상 여기가 개체의 일부 고정 된 수의 지역화하려는
really easy to generalize now your aggression had just outputs box for each
지금 당신의 침략은 단지 각 상자를 출력했다 일반화 정말 쉽게
of those objects that you care about and again you train the network in the same
당신이 걱정하고 다시 동일한에서 네트워크를 훈련하는 객체
way and this idea of actually localizing multiple objects the same time is pretty
방법과 같은 시간이 꽤입니다 실제로 현지화 여러 개체의이 아이디어
general and pretty powerful so for example this kind of approach has been
일반적으로 꽤 강력한 예를 들어 이런 종류의 접근법이있다, 그래서
used for human pose estimation so the idea is we want to input a crime a
인간의 생각은 우리가 입력 범죄 a를 원하는되도록 추정을 제기 사용
close-up view of a person and anyone to figure out what's the pose of that
근접 사람과 사람의보기를 그 포즈의 의미를 알아 내기 위해
person so well people sort of generally have a fixed number of joints like their
사람이 너무 잘 사람들은 일종의 일반적으로 같은 관절의 고정 번호가 자신의
breasts and their neck and their elbows and that sort of stuff so we just know
가슴과 목 및 팔꿈치와 재료의 종류 그래서 우리는 알고있다
that we need to find all the joints so we import our image we run it through a
우리는을 통해 실행 우리는 모든 관절을 찾아야 그래서 우리는 우리의 이미지를 가져올 수 있음
convolutional network and we regress xy coordinates for each joint location and
컨볼 루션 네트워크와 우리가 각 관절 위치에 대한 XY 좌표를 퇴보하고
that gives us our action that actually lets you predict a whole human pose
그것은 우리에게 실제로 전체 인간의 포즈를 예측할 수 있습니다 우리의 작업을 제공합니다
using the sort of localisation framework in this paper and there's a paper from
이 논문에서 지역화 프레임 워크의 종류를 사용하여 용지은있다
Google from a year or two ago that does this sort of approach that a couple
구글 일년이 전에 몇 그 방법 이런 종류의 작업을 수행 것과
other bells and whistles but the basic idea was just regressing using a CNN to
다른 종과 경적하지만 기본적인 아이디어는 단지 CNN에를 사용하여 회귀했다
these joint sessions so overall this idea of localisation and treating it as
이러한 공동 세션 그래서 전반적으로이 현지화의 아이디어로 치료
regression 46 number of objects is really really simple so I know some of
개체의 회귀 (46) 수 그래서 몇 가지를 알고 정말 정말 간단합니다
you guys on your projects have been thinking about you want to actually run
프로젝트에 너희들은 당신이 실제로 실행하려면에 대해 생각되었다
detection cause you want to understand like any parts of your images or find
검출 당신은 이미지의 어떤 부분들을 이해하거나 찾을 원인
parts inside the image and if you're thinking of a project along those lines
이미지 내부 및 경우 부분은 그 라인을 따라 프로젝트의 생각
I really encourage you to think about this localization framework instead that
난 정말 그 대신이 지역화 프레임 워크에 대해 생각해 보시기 바랍니다
if there's actually a fixed number of objects that you know you want to
당신은 당신이 원하는 알고 개체의 고정 된 수의 사실이 있다면
localize and every image you should try to frame it as a localization problem
지역화 및 모든 이미지 당신은 현지화 문제로 구도를 시도해야한다
that's tends to be a lot easier to setup alright so actually the simple idea of
즉, 많이 좋아, 그래서 실제로 설치에 쉽게 간단한 아이디어의 경향이 있어요
localisation via regression actually is really simple it'll actually work I
회귀 분석을 통해 현지화 실제로 정말 간단 실제로 I를 작동합니다
would really encourage you to try it for projects
정말 프로젝트를 위해 그것을 시도하는 것이 좋습니다 것
but if you wanna win competitions like image that you need to add a little bit
당신이하고 싶어하지만 만약 당신이 조금을 추가 할 필요가 이미지 같은 대회 우승
of other fancy stuff so another thing that people do for localisation is this
다른 멋진 물건 그래서 사람들이 현지화를 위해 할 또 다른 점은 이것이다
idea of sliding window so we'll step through this in more detail but the idea
슬라이딩 윈도우의 생각은 그래서 우리는 더 자세히하지만 생각이 단계별로합니다
is that you still have your classification localisation two-headed
당신은 여전히​​ 당신의 분류 현지화 가지고 두 향하고있다
network but you're actually gonna run it not once on the image but at multiple
네트워크는하지만 실제로 이미지에 있지만, 여러에 있지 번을 실행거야
positions on the image and you're gonna aggregated across those different
그 다른 통해 집계 된 이미지에 위치하면거야
positions and you can actually do this in an efficient way so it took sort of
그것은 일종의했다, 그래서 위치는 당신이 실제로 효율적인 방법으로이 작업을 수행 할 수 있습니다
see more concretely how how this sliding window localisation works we're gonna
보다 구체적으로이 슬라이딩 윈도우 현지화가 어떻게 작동하는지 우리는거야 방법 참조
look at the over-the-air architecture so over feat was actually the winner of the
묘기가 실제로 우승자이었다 이상의 때문에 공중파 구조를 보면
image that localisation challenge in
이미지가 2013 년 국산화에 도전
it this this architect this this sort of setup looks basically like what we saw a
그것은이이 건축가이 설정의이 종류는 기본적으로 우리가보고 무엇처럼 보인다
couple nights ago we have an Alex not at the beginning then we have a
몇 일 전에 우리는 그 다음부터 우리가 가지고에서가 아닌 알렉스가
classification had to have a regression had classification head is spinning out
분류 회귀 분류 헤드가 밖으로 돌고 있었다 있어야했다
class for us
우리 클래스
regression had a speeding up the boxes and this thing because it's in Alex nat
회귀는 알렉스 NAT에있어 때문에이 상자와이 일을 가속화했다
type of architecture is expecting an input of 221 221 but actually we can run
구조의 유형은 221 (221)의 입력을 기대하지만 실제로 우리는 실행할 수 있습니다
this on larger images and this can help sometimes so suppose we have a large
큰 사진이 때로는 도움이 될 수 있습니다에이 그래서 우리는 큰 있다고 가정
larger image of what and when I say 257 by 257 now we could imagine taking our
내가 257에 의해 257를 말할 때 지금 우리가 복용 상상할 수있는 무엇의 큰 이미지를 우리
classification + localisation network and running at just on the upper corner
분류 + 현지화 네트워크 그냥 상단 모서리에 실행
of this image and that'll give us some some class score and also some summer
본 이미지는 그 어떤 여름 우리에게 일부 어떤 수준의 점수를주지
grass bounding box and we're gonna repeat this take our same classification
잔디 경계 상자 우리는 거 반복있어이 우리 같은 구분을
+ localisation network and run it on all four corners of this image and after
+ 현지화 네트워크와이 이미지의 이후 네 모서리에서 실행
doing so will end up with for grass bounding boxes one from each of those
이렇게하면 사람들의 각각에서 잔디 경계 박스 하나에 종료됩니다
four locations together with a class classification score for each location
각 위치에 대한 클래스 분류 점수와 함께 4 개소
but we actually want just a single bounding box so then they use some
그러나 우리는 실제로는 일부를 사용 그럼 단지 하나의 경계 상자를 원하는
heuristics to Mercedes bounding boxes in scores and that puts a little bit ugly I
메르세데스 점수에 상자를 경계하고 조금 못생긴 I을두고하는 휴리스틱
don't wanna go into the details here they have it in the paper but the idea
싶지 않아 그들은 종이지만 생각에이 여기에 세부 사항으로 이동
is that public combining aggregating these boxes across multiple locations
그 대중은 여러 위치에서이 상자를 집계 결합한다
can help that can help the model sort of credits on airs and this tends to work
그 방송 해에 크레딧의 모델 정렬을 할 수 있습니다 도움이 작동하는 경향이 있습니다
really well and that mean that won them the challenge that year
정말 잘 그 해 그들에게 도전을 수상하는 평균
but in practice they actually use many more than four locations
하지만 실제로 그들은 실제로 많은 개 이상의 위치를​​ 사용
oh ya ought to be fully with them
오, 나중에는 그들과 함께 완벽하게되어야한다
well I mean it's actually good point so once you're doing regression you're just
잘 난 그냥있어 당신이 회귀하고있어 한 번, 그래서 실제로 좋은 지적 뜻
predicting for numbers you couldn't crack you couldn't be reproduced
번호를 예측하는 것은 당신이 복제되지 않을 수 균열 없습니다
anywhere it doesn't have to be inside the image although I know that brings up
어디서나 내가 그납니다 알고 있지만 이미지 내에서 할 필요는 없습니다
a good point when you're doing this especially when they when you're
그들은 당신이있을 때 때 특히이 일을하고 좋은 점
training this network in this sliding window way you actually to ship the
이 슬라이딩 윈도우 방식으로이 네트워크를 훈련하면 실제로 발송하기
ground truth box in a little bit ship ship the coordinate frame for those
약간 선박 선박 지상 진실 상자가 사람들을 위해 프레임을 조정
different slices that's kind of an ugly details just worried about ya but in
나중에 약하지만 단지 걱정 못생긴 세부 종류의 서로 다른 조각
practice they use many more than four image locations and they actually do
그들은 많은 개 이상의 이미지의 위치를​​ 사용하여 실제로 수행 연습
multiple scales as well as you can see this is actually figure from their paper
뿐만 아니라 당신이 볼 수있는 여러 규모는 실제로 종이로 파악된다
I'm a left you see all the different positions where they kind of evaluated
나는 당신이 그들이 가지 평가 모두 다른 위치를 참조 남아있어
this network in the middle you see those output progressed boxes one for each of
중간에이 네트워크는 그 출력의 각 상자를 하나씩 진행 참조
those positions on the bottom easy to score map for each of those positions
하단 쉬운에 그 위치는 그 위치 각각에 대해지도를 득점 할 수
and then I mean they're pretty noisy but it's kinda convert their kind of
다음 나는 그들이 매우 시끄러운하지만 좀 자신의 종류를 변환있어 의미
generally over the bear so they'd run this fancy aggregation method and they
일반적으로 곰을 통해 그들은이 멋진 집계 방법을 실행하고 줄 수 있도록
get a final box for the bear and they decide that the same as a pair and they
곰에 대한 최종 상자를 얻을하고 결정하는 한 쌍의 그들과 동일
actually won the challenge with this but one problem you might anticipate is it
실제로이와 도전을 원하지만 예상 할 수 하나의 문제는이다
could be pretty expensive to actually run the network on every one of those
실제로 그 하나 하나의 네트워크를 실행하는 데 꽤 비싼 될 수 있습니다
crops but there's actually more efficient with thing we could do so we
작물하지만 우리는 우리가 할 수있는 일에 실제로 더 효율적인있다
normally think of these networks as having convolutional errors and then
일반적으로 다음 길쌈 오류을 갖는 이러한 네트워크의 생각
fully connected Lares but when you think about it
완전히 수호신 연결하지만 당신은 그것에 대해 생각할 때
a fully connected larry is just 4096 numbers right it's just a factor but
완전히 연결 래리 단지 4096 번호를 잘 그냥 요인이다하지만
instead of thinking of it as a vector we could think of it as just another
대신 벡터로 생각의 우리는 그것으로 또 다른 생각을 할 수
convolutional feature map is kinda crazy we just transpose that added to
길쌈 기능지도 좀 미친 우리는 단지에 추가 트랜스
one-by-one dimensions so now the idea is that we can now treat our car fully
하나씩 크기 그래서 지금 생각은 우리가 지금 완전히 우리의 차를 처리 할 수​​ 있다는 것입니다
connected layers and convert them into convolutional there's a few imagined in
연결된 레이어와의 상상 몇 가지있다 길쌈로 변환
our fully connected network we had this convolutional feature map and we had one
우리의 완전히 연결된 네트워크는 우리는이 길쌈 기능지도를 가지고 있었고, 우리는 하나가 있었다
way from each element of that competition will feature map to produce
생산지도 기능을합니다 그 경쟁의 각 요소에서 방법
each element of our 4096 dimensional vector but we instead of thinking about
각 우리의 4096 차원 벡터의 요소 그러나 우리 대신에 대해 생각
reshaping and having a fine layer that's sort of equivalent to just having a five
재편 및 정렬 단지 다섯 가지는 중 상당의 벌금 층을 갖는
by five
오에 의해
solution it's a little bit weird but if you think about it it should make sense
솔루션은 조금 이상한하지만 당신이 그것에 대해 생각하면 그것은 이해한다
eventually but alright so then we take this fully connected later turns into a
결국하지만 확실히 그래서 우리는 나중에로 변신이 완전히 연결 취할
five by five convolution than this than we previously had another fully
우리가 이전에 완전히 다른 것보다이 최대 5 회선에 의한 오
connected mayor going from 4096 4096 this is actually a one-by-one
4096 4096이에서가 연결 시장은 실제로 하나씩입니다
convolution right that's that's kinda weird but if you if you think hard and
당신은 당신이 열심히 생각하면 경우에 그 좀 이상한입니다 만 회선 오른쪽
work out the math on paper and go send a quiet room you'll figure it out and so
종이에 수학을 해결하고 조용한 방을 보내 가서 당신이 그것을 알아낼 그래서 것
we basically can't earn each of these fully connected layers and our network
우리는 기본적으로이 완전히 연결 레이어와 우리의 네트워크의 각을 얻을 수 없습니다
into a convolutional air and now now this is pretty cool because now our
길쌈 공기에 지금 지금이 때문에 지금은 정말 멋진 우리의
network is composed entirely of just contributions and pooling and elements
네트워크는 기여와 풀링 및 요소를 완전히 구성되어있다
operations so now we can actually run the network on images of different sizes
작업은 이제 우리는 실제로 서로 다른 크기의 이미지에 네트워크를 실행할 수 있도록
and this sort of will give us very cheaply equip the equivalent of
그리고 이런 종류의 매우 저렴한 비용으로 우리에게 동등한를 장착합니다
operating but not work independently on different locations so to kind of see
그래서 볼의 종류에 다른 위치에서 독립적으로 작동하지 않을 수 있지만 운영
how that works
어떻게 작동
you imagine a training time you may be working over 14 by 14 template you run
당신은 당신이 실행 14 템플릿에 의해 당신이 14 이상 작업 할 수있는 교육 시간을 상상
some convolutions and then here are are fully connected layers that we're now
여기에는 일부 회선과 우리가 지금이야 완전히 연결 층입니다
re-imagining as convolutional Ayers said and we have this by by five con block
재 상상으로 길쌈 즈가 말했다, 우리는 다섯 콘 블록이로이
that gets turned into these one-by-one specially sized elements so we've sort
우리가 정렬했습니다 그래서 이러한 하나씩 특별히 크기의 요소로 설정됩니다
of eliminating not showing the depth dimension here but these like this one
이 같은하지 제거 여기에 깊이 치수를 표시하지만, 이들의
by one would be one by one by 4096 rights or just converting these layers
하나 4096 권한에 의해 하나 하나가 될하거나 이러한 레이어를 변환하는 것
into a convolutional there's now that we know that their convolutions we could
길쌈에 우리가 알고있는 지금 거기에 자신의 회선 우리가 할 수 그
actually run on in part of a larger size and you can see that now we've got we've
실제로 더 큰 크기의 부분에 실행하고 당신은 지금 우리가했습니다 가지고 있음을 알 수
added a couple extra pixels and now we actually run all these things the
몇 가지 추가 픽셀을 추가하고 지금 우리는 실제로이 모든 것을을 실행
convolutions and get a two-by-two output but what's really cool here is that
회선 및 두 개의 별 두 개의 출력을 얻을 수 있지만, 어떻게 여기 정말 멋진 것입니다
we're able to share computation to make this really efficient so now our output
우리는이 정말 효율적 그래서 지금 우리의 출력을 만들기 위해 계산을 공유 할 수있어
is four times as big but we've done much less than four times the compute cuz if
큰 4 배하지만 우리는 훨씬 적은보다 4 배의 경우 사촌 컴퓨팅을했습니다
you think about the difference between where we're doing computation here the
여기에 우리가하고있는 계산의 차이에 대해 생각
only extra computation happened in these yellow parts so now we're actually very
만 여분의 계산은 지금이 노란색 부분에서 일어난 우리는 실제로 매우있어
efficiently evaluating the network at many many different positions without
효율적없이 많은 다양한 위치에서 네트워크를 평가
actually spending much computation so this is how they're able to evaluate
이 그들이 평가할 수있어 얼마나 그래서 실제로 많은 계산을 지출
that network in that very very dense multiscale way that you saw a couple
당신은 몇 보았다 아주 아주 조밀 한 다중 스케일 방법으로 해당 네트워크
nights ago that make sense any questions on this
확인 전에 밤이에 대한 질문을 감지
ok writes actually we can look at the classification + localisation results on
확인 쓰기는 실제로 우리의 분류 + 현지화 결과를 볼 수 있습니다
a mission over the last couple of years so in 2012 Alex Alex Kozinski Jack
그래서 2012 년 알렉스 알렉스 Kozinski 잭에서 지난 몇 년 동안 임무
Hinton they won not only classification but also localisation but I wasn't able
힌튼은뿐만 아니라 분류뿐만 아니라 현지화를 원하지만 난 수 없습니다
to find any published details of exactly how they did that in 2013 was the
그들은 2013 년을 것을 어떻게했는지 정확히의 게시 된 내용을 찾을 수
over-the-top that we just saw actually improved on Alex's results a little bit
이상 - 더 - 상단 우리가 실제로 알렉스의 결과 조금에 개선 보았다
the year after we talked about VGG and they're sort of really deep 19 their
올해 우리는 VGG에 대해 얘기하고 일종의 정말 깊은 19 야 후 자신의
network they got second place on classification but actually 1 I'm
네트워크 그들은 분류에 두번째 장소를 가지고 있지만 난 실제로 1
localisation and the BGG actually used basically exactly the same strategy that
현지화와 BGG 실제로 기본적으로 정확히 같은 전략을 사용하는
over feat dead they just use the deeper network and actually interesting the BGG
위업의 죽음을 통해 그들은 단지 더 깊은 네트워크를 사용하고 실제로 BGG 흥미로운
used fewer scales they stand pat network out in fewer places and used fewer
사용 된 적은 규모는 적은 장소에서 팻 네트워크를 눈에 띄는 적게 사용
skills but they actually decrease the era quite a bit so basically the only
기술은 있지만 실제로 그렇게 기본적으로 시대에게 유일한 상당히 감소
difference being over feet and BG here is that BGU the deeper network so here
차이는 피트 이상되는 및 BG는 여기에 BGU 깊은 네트워크 그래서 여기에
we could see that these really powerful image features actually improve the
우리는이 정말 강력한 이미지 기능을 실제로 향상을 볼 수
localization performance quite a bit with enough to change the localisation
현지화를 변경하기에 충분와 현지화 성능 꽤
architecture at all we just swapped out about her CNN and it improved results a
아키텍처는 전혀 우리는 단지 그녀의 CNN 대해 교환과 결과 a를 개선
lot and then this year in 2015 Microsoft swept everything as that'll be a theme
그 테마가 될 것으로 2015 년 많은 후 올해 마이크로 소프트는 모든 것을 휩쓸
in this lecture as well this this hundred fifty lair ResNet from Microsoft
Microsoft에서 제공하는이 강의는 물론이이 치고 은신처 ResNet에서
crushed localisation here and drunk proper performance from 25 all the way
25 모든 방법에서 여기 현지화 및 음주 적절한 성능을 짓 눌린
down to nine but I mean this this is a little bit and this is talk to really
하지만 구까지 나는이이 조금 의미하고 이것은 정말 이야기입니다
isolate the deep features so yes they did have deeper features but Microsoft
깊은 기능을 분리 그래서 예 그들은 깊은 기능을하지만 마이크로 소프트가 않았다
actually it's a different localization method called rpms region proposal
실제로 다른 지역화 방법이라고 RPM을 지역 제안이다
networks so it's not really clear whether this which part whether it's a
네트워크 정말 분명하지 않다, 그래서 그것이인지이 어느 부분인지
better localization strategy or whether the better features but at any rate they
더 나은 현지화 전략 또는 더 나은 기능 여부 그러나 어떤 속도로 그들
did really well that's pretty much all I want to say about classification
정말 잘이 꽤 많이 나는 분류에 대해 말하고 싶은 전부 않았다
localisation just consider doing it for projects and if there's any questions
질문이 있다면 현지화는 프로젝트를 위해 그 일을 고려하고
about this task we should talk about that now before moving on ya
이 작업에 대해 우리는 지금 나중에에 이동하기 전에 그것에 대해 이야기해야
performance especially with a loss right so then I'll two losses when having
바로 그럼 내가이 손실을 갖는 것이다 때 특히 손실 성능
outliers is actually really bad so sometimes people don't use an L to loss
아웃 라이어 그래서 때때로 사람들은 손실에 L을 사용하지 않는 사실은 정말 나쁜
instead you can try and sell one loss that can help with outliers a little bit
대신 시도하고 아웃 라이어 약간의 도움이 될 수 있습니다 하나의 손실을 판매 할 수 있습니다
people also will do sometimes a smooth one loss where it looks like he'll one
그는 하나를 거처럼 보이는 곳 사람들은 때로는 부드러운 하나의 손실을 다할 것입니다
sort of a tales but then near zero it'll be quadratic so actually swapping out
이야기의 종류하지만 제로 근처는 차있을거야 실제로 스와핑 때문에
that regression loss function can help a bit with outliers sometimes but also if
그 회귀 손실 함수는 때때로뿐만 아니라 경우에 아웃 라이어와 약간의 도움이 될 수 있습니다
you have a little bit of noise sometimes hopefully you're not just figured out
당신은 때때로 희망 당신은 그냥 생각하지 않는 소음이 약간 있습니다
cross your fingers don't think too hard questions questions so people do both
사람들이 모두 할 수 있도록 손가락이 너무 어려운 질문 질문을 생각하지 않는다 교차
actually I'm so over feet actually I don't remember I don't remember exactly
실제로 나는 실제로 그렇게 피트이야 내가 정확히 기억하지 못하는 기억하지 않는다
which oversee dead but BGG actually backdrops into the entire network so
이는 죽은 감독하지만 BGG 실제로 때문에 전체 네트워크에 배경막
it'll be it'll be faster to just actually work fine if you just trained
그냥 훈련을받은 경우는 실제로 잘 작동이 빠른에있을거야 수 있습니다
in the regression had but you'll tend to get a little bit better results if you
회귀에했지만, 당신은 당신이 경우 조금 더 나은 결과를 얻을하는 경향이 있습니다
back drop into the home network and BG did this experiment and they got maybe
다시 홈 네트워크에 드롭 BG는이 실험을했고, 그들은 아마있어
one or two points extra buyback dropping through the whole thing but it at the
상기 하나 또는 두 개의 점을 추가 매입의 모든 일을 통해 낙하하지만,
expense of a lot more competition and training time so it so I would I would
더 많은 경쟁과 훈련 시간의 비용 그래서 그래서 나는 것 나는 것
say it like as a first thing don't just talk tried not back dropping and the
그냥 시도 얘기하지 않는 우선으로 다시 삭제하고 있지처럼 말
network
네트워크
generally not right because your testing on the same classes that you saw
일반적으로하지 못하기 때문에 당신이 본 동일한 클래스에 대한 테스팅
training time you're gonna see different instances obviously but I mean you're
당신이거야 교육 시간은 분명히 다른 인스턴스를 참조하지만 난 당신이있어 의미
still bears a tough time in OC bears at training time we're not expecting you to
여전히 우리는 당신을 기대하지 않는 교육 시간에 OC 곰에서 힘든 시간을 곰
generalize across classes I'll be pretty hard
내가 꽤 어려울 것이다 클래스에서 일반화
yea good question yes so sometimes people will do that they'll train with
참 좋은 질문은 네 그래서 때때로 사람들은 함께 훈련을하고 있다고 할 것입니다
both simultaneously also sometimes people will just end up with separate
모두 동시에 또한 때때로 사람들은 별도로 끝날 것
networks one that sort of only responsible for aggression when it's
네트워크 종류의 책임 침략에 대한 그것의 하나를
only responsible for classification those both work well glad you asked
이들 모두는 질문도 기쁜 일을 분류 만 책임
that's that's actually the next thing we're gonna talk about that's that's a
그는 실제로 우리가가가의의에 대해 거 이야기하고있는 다음 일이있어
different task of object detection so
객체 검출의 다른 과제 그래서
well yeah well so I mean it kinda depends on the training strategy if
물론 그래 내 말 잘 그래서 좀 훈련 전략 경우에 따라 달라집니다
you're like if you also kind of goes back to this idea of class agnostic
당신은 또한 종류의 불가지론 클래스의이 아이디어로 돌아갑니다 경우 같은거야
first-class Pacific regression class agnostic regression it doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다 일류 태평양 회귀 클래스 무관 회귀
you just regress to the boxes tomorrow the class class specific you're sort of
당신은 당신이 일종의있어 클래스 클래스 특정 내일 상자에 회귀
training separate aggressors for each class right let's talk about object
각 클래스에 대해 별도의 침략자를 훈련하는 것은 권리의 객체에 대해 이야기하자
detection so object detection is is much fancier much cooler but also a lot
객체 검출하므로 검출은 훨씬 더 많은 냉각 애호가이지만
harrier so the idea is that again we have an input image we have some sort of
해리는 그렇게 생각은 우리가 입력 이미지를 가지고 다시 우리의 일종을 가지고있다
classes we want to find all instances of those classes in that in that input
클래스는 우리가 입력에 있다는 점에서 그 클래스의 모든 인스턴스를 찾으려면
image so I mean you know regression worked pretty well for localisation why
내 말은, 그래서 이미지는 회귀 현지화 이유에 대해 꽤 잘 작동 알고
don't we try it for for detection to mark as an SMS we have these these dogs
우리는 탐지가 SMS로 표시하기 위해 시도하지 않습니다 우리는이이 개를
and cats and we have four things we have 16 numbers thats looks like that looks
고양이와 우리가 네 가지를 가지고 우리는 그게 전부가 보이는 것 같습니다 16 번호가
like regression rate image in numbers out but if we look at another image then
수의 회귀 율 이미지 밖으로하지만 우리는 다른 이미지를 보면 다음과 같은
you know this one only has two things coming out so it has eight numbers they
이 하나의 단지 그것을 팔 수를 갖도록 나오는 두 가지가 알고있는 그들은
look at this one there's a whole bunch of cats we need a bunch of numbers so I
고양이의 모두 거기에이 일을보고 우리가 숫자의 무리를 필요로 난 그렇게
mean it's it's kind of hard to treat detection a straight-up regression
그것은 검출에게 스트레이트 업 회귀를 치료하는 종류의 하드의 뜻
because we have this problem of variable size outputs so we're gonna have to do
우리가 거​​해야하고, 그래서 우리는 가변 크기의 출력이 문제를 가지고 있기 때문에
something fancier although actually there is a method will talk about later
실제로이 있지만 애호가 뭔가 방법이 나중에에 대해 이야기합니다
that sort of does this anyway and does treated as as regression but we'll get
그런 종류의 어쨌든이 작업을 수행하고 회귀 등으로 처리 않지만 우리는거야
to that we'll get to that later but in general you wanna not treat this as
그에게 우리는 그 이상으로 얻을 것이다 그러나 일반적으로 당신은이 취급하지 싶어
regression because you have very precise outputs so we're really easy problem
회귀 우리가 정말 쉬운 문제가있어, 그래서 매우 정확한 출력을 가지고 있기 때문에
really easy way to solve this is to think of detection not as regression but
이 문제를 해결하기 정말 쉬운 방법이 검출 생각하지 회귀로하지만,
as classification right in machine learning regression and classification
기계의 분류 권리로 회귀 및 분류를 학습
are your two hammers you just want to use those to eat all your problems right
당신이 망치는 그냥 모든 문제를 바로 먹는 사람들을 사용할 수 있습니다
so we regression and works will do classification instead we know how to
그래서 대신에 우리가 방법을 알고 우리는 회귀 작품 분류를 할 것입니다
classify image regions we just for CNN right we're going to do is we're gonna
우리는거야 우리가 그냥 CNN의 권리를 위해 우리가 할거야 이미지 영역을 분류
take many of these input regions of the image of a classifier there and say like
거기 분류의 영상이 입력 많은 지역을과 같은 말
alright this region of the alleged attack at No
확실히에서 추정 된 공격이 지역 없음
as a dog know that over a little bit we found a cat that's great but over a
개 같이 조금 이상 우리가 큰하지만 끝났어 고양이를 발견 것을 알고있다
little bit that's that's not anything so then we can actually just try out a
우리가 실제로 단지를 시도 할 수 있도록 그 아무것도 아니다이야 조금
whole bunch different image regions run a classifier in each one and this will
전체 무리 다른 이미지 영역은 각각이 뜻에서 분류를 실행
basically solve our variable size output problem
기본적으로 우리 가변 크기 출력 문제를 해결
so there's there's no question so the question of how decide how to decide
그래서 결정 방법의 문제는 방법을 결정할 수 있도록 더 문제가 없습니다 거기에
what the window size the answer is we just tried them all right just literally
어떤 창 크기 대답하는 것은 우리가 모든 권리 그냥 그대로을 시도하다
tried them all so that's that's that's actually a big problem right because we
즉 그가 우리 때문에 오른쪽 실제로 큰 문제입니다입니다 그래서 그들 모두를 시도
need to try Windows of different sizes of different positions of different
다른 여러 위치의 서로 다른 크기의 윈도우를 시도해야
scales me do this properly test and this is going to be really expensive right
날이 제대로 테스트 할 비늘이 정말 비싼 잘 될 것입니다
there's a whole lot of places we need to look yeah also when you're doing this
당신이이 일을 할 때 우리는 그래도 볼 필요가 장소의 전체 많아요
you add an extra two things one you can add an extra class to say background and
당신이 여분의 두 가지 하나가 말을 별도의 클래스를 추가 할 수 있습니다 추​​가 배경
say like oh there's nothing here another thing you can do is not is to actually
여기에 당신이 할 수있는 또 다른 것은 사실이다하지 않습니다 같은 오 거기에 아무것도 말
multi-label classification you cannot put multiple positive things right
다중 레이블 분류는 바로 여러 긍정적 인 물건을 넣을 수 없습니다
that's actually pretty easy to do and just instead of a soft max loss you have
그것은 할 사실은 아주 쉽게 그냥 대신 당신이 가진 부드러운 최대 손실이다
independent regression loss of independent logistic regression class so
독립적 인 로지스틱 회귀 클래스의 독립적 인 회귀 손실 때문에
I can actually let you say yes I multiple classes at one point but that's
나는 실제로 당신이 네 말을 나는 여러 클래스의 한 지점에서 할 수 있지만 그건
just walking on a loss function so that's that's pretty easy to do right so
다만 손실 함수에 걸어 그래서 그게 바로 이렇게 아주 쉽다이다
actually like what we see a problem with this approach is that there's a whole
우리는이 방법에 문제가 보는 것을 실제로 전체가 거기에 있는지처럼
bunch of different positions we need to evaluate the solution sort of a couple
다른 위치의 무리 우리는 몇 가지의 솔루션 정렬을 평가해야
you as a couple of years ago was just usually class fat used really fast
몇 년 전이었다 당신은 보통 수준의 지방은 정말 빨리 사용
classifiers try them all so actually detection is this really all problem in
분류 그래서 실제로 검출이 정말 모든 문제에 그들 모두를 시도
computer vision so you should probably have a little bit more historical
컴퓨터 비전 당신은 아마 조금 더 기록해야하므로
perspective so starting in about 2005 there was this really successful
관점 그래서이 정말 성공 거기에 대해 2005 년에 시작
approach to it but I'm really successful detection that use this feature
그것에 접근하지만이 기능을 사용 정말 성공적으로 검출 해요
representation called histograms of Oriented radiance so if you are call
당신이 전화 그래서 만약 표현을 지향 광채의 히스토그램을 호출
back to homework 1 you actually use this feature on the last part to actually do
다시 숙제 1 당신은 실제로 실제로 할 수있는 마지막 부분에이 기능을 사용
classification as well so this was actually a sort of the best feature that
분류도 그래서 이것은 실제로 가장 큰 특징 일종의였습니다
we had in computer vision Sircar in 2005 the idea is we're just gonna do linear
우리는 아이디어는 우리가 선형 그냥 야 할 것입니다 2005 년에 컴퓨터 비전 나리에 있었다
classifiers on top of this feature and that's going to be our our classifier so
이 기능의 상단에 분류하고 그래서 우리의 우리의 분류 될 것
linear classifiers are really fast so if this works is that we compute are
선형 분류는이 작품 그래서 만약 것은 우리가 계산이다 빠르고 정말
oriented gradient feature for the whole image at multiple scales and we run this
여러 규모에서 전체 이미지에 그라데이션 기능을 지향하고 우리는 이것을 실행
linear classifier at every scale every position just do it really fast just do
모든 위치가 그냥 정말 빨리 바로 수행 할 모든 규모의 선형 분류
it everywhere
모든 곳
classifier and its past to evaluate
분류 및 과거 평가할
and this worked really well in 2005 sort of people took this idea and worked on
이것은 이런 생각을했다 사람 2005 종류에 정말 잘 근무에 일
it a little bit more in the next couple of years so sort of the one of the most
그것 때문에 일종의 앞으로 몇 년 가장의 일에 조금 더
important detection paradigms 3d planning is this thing called deep but
중요한 검출 차원의 계획이 일 깊은이라고 패러다임하지만,
deformable parts model so I don't wanna go too much into the details are best
변형 부품 모델은 그래서 싶어 너무 많은 세부 최고에 가지 마세요
but I mean the basic idea is that we're still working on these history memorial
하지만 기본적인 아이디어는 우리가 아직도이 역사 기념관에 최선을 다하고 있음을 의미
gradient features but now our model rather than just being a linear
그라데이션 기능을하지만 지금은 우리의 모델보다는 선형 인
classifier we have this linear click this linear sort of template for the
분류 우리는이 선형이를위한 템플릿이 선형 종류를 클릭해야
object and we also have these templates for parts that are allowed to sort of
객체 그리고 우리는 또한 정렬 할 수 있습니다 부품에 대한 이러한 템플릿을
very over spatial positions and deform a little bit and they have some some fancy
매우 공간적 위치를 통해 조금 변형하고 일부 약간의 공상을 가지고
fancy think about late in the AM to learn these things and really fancy
공상은 이러한 것들을 정말 멋진 내용을 보려면 오전에 대해 말 생각
dynamic programming algorithms actually evaluate this thing really fast test
동적 프로그래밍 알고리즘은 실제로 정말 빨리 시험이 일을 평가
time is actually kind of fun if you enjoy our thumbs this this thing at this
이에 우리의 엄지 손가락이이 일을 즐길 경우 시간이 실제로 종류의 재미
part is kind of fun to think about but the end result is that it's it's a much
부분은 재미의 종류에 대해 생각하지만 최종 결과는 그것이 훨씬이다라는 것이다
more powerful classifier that allows a little bit of deformability in your
에 변형성 조금 있습니다 더 강력한 분류하여
model and you can still about weight really fast so we're still just going to
모델 당신은 여전히​​ 체중에 대해 정말 빠른 그래서 우리는 여전히 그냥 갈거야 수 있습니다
evaluate it everywhere every scale every position every aspect ratio just do it
그냥 해 모든 규모를 어디서나 모든 화면 비율을 모든 위치를 평가
everywhere its past and this actually worked really well in 2010 around there
사방 과거이 실제로 주위 2010 년에 정말로 잘했다
that was sort of state of the art and detection for many problems at a time so
그 때문에 한 번에 많은 문제를위한 기술 및 검출 상태의 일종이었다
this is I don't spend too much time on this but there was a really cool paper
이것은 내가이 너무 많은 시간을 할애하지 않지만 정말 멋진 종이가 있었다
last year that argued that these dpi models are actually just a certain type
이 dpi의 모델은 실제로 단지 특정 유형한다고 주장 작년
of content right and so right
콘텐츠 권리 등 권리의
these these history I'm going crazy ants are like little edges we can just look
이 이러한 역사 나는거야 미친 개미는 우리가 볼 수 약간의 가장자리처럼
on delusions and history and was kinda like pooling that sort of thing so if
망상과 역사와 있었다 좀 그런 종류의 물건을 풀링 등에 그렇다면
you're interested check out this paper it's kind of fun to think about right
당신은 권리에 대해 생각하는 재미의 종류의이 논문을 관심을 확인하고
but we really want to work on
그러나 우리는 정말 작업 할
make this thing work on classifiers that are not fast without weights like maybe
아마 같은 무게없이 빠른없는 분류에이 일을 작동하게
a CNN so here this week this problem is still hard right we have many different
CNN과 그래서 여기에 이​​번 주이 문제는 여전히 우리가 다른 많은이 하드 맞아
positions you want to try when we probably can't actually afford to try
우리가 아마 실제로 시도 할 여유가 없을 때 시도하려는 배치
them all so the solution is that we don't try them all we have some other
모두 있도록 솔루션은 우리가 다른이 그들 모두를 시도하지 않는다는 것입니다
things that sort of guesses where we want to look and then we only apply our
것을 우리가보고 싶어하고 우리는 우리의 적용 추측의 종류
expense of classifier at those smaller number of locations so that idea
그 생각 때문에 위치의 그 작은 수에서 분류의 비용
is called region proposals so we on our region proposal method is this thing
우리 지역의 제안 방법에 우리가이 일 때문에 지역 제안이라고
that takes in an image and then outputs a whole bunch of regions where maybe
그 이미지에 소요 다음 경우 어쩌면 지역의 전체 무리를 출력
possibly an object might be located so one way you can think about region
하나의 방법이 지역에 대해 생각할 수 있도록 가능한 개체는 찾을 수 있습니다
proposals is that they're kinda like a really fast
제안은 좀 정말 빠른 같아 것입니다
class agnostic object detector right they don't care about the class they're
클래스 불가지론 개체 검출기는 바로 그들이있어 클래스에 대해 걱정하지 않는다
not very accurate but they're pretty fast to run and they give us a whole
하지 매우 정확하지만 그들은 실행 꽤 빨리있어, 그들이 우리에게 전체를 제공
bunch of boxes and the general intuition behind behind these region proposal
상자의 무리와이 지역의 제안 뒤에 뒤에 일반 직관
methods is that they're kinda looking for blob like structure is an image rate
방법들이 좀 구조 등의 얼룩을 찾는 것을하는 것은 이미지 속도입니다
so like objects are generally the dog i mean if you can ask when it looks kinda
그래서 개체는 일반적으로 내가 그것을 좀 보이는 때 요청할 수 있다면 의미 강아지처럼
like a white blob the cat looks like a white blobs flowers I kinda blah be the
고양이가 흰색 얼룩 꽃처럼 보이는 흰색 덩어리처럼 나는 일종의 될 ㅋ
eyes and nose are kinda blah be so anyone these region proposal methods a
눈과 코는 좀 ㅋ 수 있으므로 사람이 지역의 제안, 메소드이다
lot of times what you'll see is the kind of put boxes around a lot of these
당신이 볼 무엇 시대의 많은 이들의 많은 주위에 넣어 상자의 종류
blobby regions in the image so probably the most famous region proposal method
이미지의 blobby 영역 그래서 아마 가장 유명한 지역 제안 방법
is called selective search you don't really need to know exact into much
선택적 검색이라고 당신은 정말 많은으로 정확히 알 필요가 없습니다
detail how this works but the idea is that you start from your pixels and you
이 아이디어에 불과 어떻게 작동하는지 세부 사항은 당신이 당신의 픽셀과 당신부터 시작이다
kind of merger adjacent pixels together if they have similar color and texture
그들이 유사한 색상과 질감이 함께있는 경우 합병 인접 화소의 종류
and form these are connected reid disconnected blob like regions and then
다음 지역과 같은이 연결되어있는 리드 연결이 끊긴 덩어리를 형성
you merge yuppies blob like regions to get bigger and bigger body parts and
당신이 더 크고 더 큰 신체 부위를 얻을 수있는 지역 등 여피족의 얼룩을 병합
then for each of these different scales you could actually convert each of these
다음이 다른 스케일의 각각에 대해 실제로 이들 각각을 변환 할 수 있습니다
Bobby regions into a box by just drawing a box around it so then by doing this
그냥이 작업을 수행하여 그럼 주위에 상자를 그려서 상자에 바비 영역
over multiple scales you end up with a whole bunch of boxes around sort of a
여러 저울을 통해 당신은 일종의 주위에 상자의 전체 무리와 끝까지
lot of blobby stuff in the image and its are reasonably fast to compute and
이미지의 blobby 물건을 많이하고이 계산 합리적으로 신속하고
actually cuts down the search space quite a lot but selectively certainly
실제로 검색 공간을 선택적으로 확실히 꽤 많이 있지만 아래로 인하
isn't the only game in town is just may be the most famous there's a whole bunch
마을의 유일한 게임이 바로 가장 유명한 될 수있다되지 않는 것은 왕창있다
of different region proposal methods that people have developed there was
거기 사람들이 개발의 다른 지역 제안 방법
this paper last year that actually did a really cool thorough scientific
이 논문은 작년에 실제로 정말 멋진 철저한 과학을 행한
evaluation of all these different region proposal methods and sort of gave you
종류 모든 다른 지역의 제안 방법 및 평가의 준
the pros and the cons of each and all that kind of stuff but I mean my
프로와 각각의 단점과 물건의 모든 종류하지만 내 말은 내
takeaway from this paper was just use that boxes if you had to pick one so
이 논문에서 테이크 아웃은했다 상자에게 그렇게 하나를 선택해야한다면 것을 사용
it's it's it's really fast it you can run it in the bottom third of a second
그것은 정말 빨리가 두 번째의 바닥 세 번째에 실행할 수있어입니다입니다
per image compared to about 10 seconds for selective search
선택적 검색을위한 약 10 초에 비해 이미지 당
but more stars is better and it gets a lot of stars so it's going right so now
하지만 더 많은 별이 더 나은 그것이 지금 바로거야 그래서 별을 많이 얻는다
that we have this idea region proposals and we have this idea of a CNN
우리는이 아이디어 지역의 제안을 가지고 우리는 CNN의 이런 생각을 가지고
classifier let's just put everything altogether so that's and so this this
분류는 그 등이이 그래서 그냥 전부 다 넣어 보자
idea was sort of first put together in a really nice way in 2014 in this method
아이디어는 일종의 먼저이 방법으로 2014 년에 정말 좋은 방법으로 함께 넣어
called RCN on the idea is it's a region-based CNN method so it's it's
그것의 그래서 아이디어라고 RCN IT는 영역 - 기반 방법이다 CNN된다
it's pretty simple man what we've seen all the pieces we have an input image
우리가 우리가 입력 이미지가 모든 조각을 본 적이 무엇을 아주 간단 사람입니다
we're gonna run a region proposal method like selective search to get about maybe
선택적 검색에 대한 아마 얻을처럼 우린 영역 제안 방법을 실행하고
two thousand boxes of different scales and positions mean 2000 still a lot but
이천 다른 스케일의 상자와 위치 2000을 의미 여전히 많이 있지만,
it's a lot less than all possible boxes in the image now for each of those boxes
그것은 그 상자의 각각에 대해 이제 이미지의 모든 가능한 상자보다 훨씬 더 적은이다
we're gonna have cropped and warp that image region to some fixed size and then
우리는 그 다음 자른 어떤 고정 된 크기로 그 이미지 영역을 워프하고있는거야
run it former through I CNN to classify and then this CNN is going to have a
분류하기 나는 CNN을 통해이 전 실행 한 다음이 CNN은해야 할 것입니다
regression head and the regression had here and a classification had been used
회귀 헤드와 회귀 여기 있었고 분류 사용되었던
as PM's here so the idea is that this this regression had can sort of correct
PM은 여기로 생각이이 회귀 할 수있는 일종의 올바른 것으로 그래서
for region proposals that were a little bit off writes this this actually works
있었다 영역의 제안에 대해 조금 떨어져이이 실제로 작동 기록
really well it's really simple yeah it's pretty cool but unfortunately so
정말 잘 그래 정말 간단있어 정말 멋진하지만, 불행히도 그렇게
unfortunately the training pipeline is a little bit complicated so the way that
불행하게도 교육 파이프 라인은 조금 길 있도록 복잡하게된다
you end up train training src and a model is you know like many like many
당신은 기차 훈련 SRC를 종료하고 모델은 많은 같은 많은처럼 알고있다
models you first start by downloading a model from the internet that works well
모델이 먼저 잘 작동 인터넷에서 모델을 다운로드하여 시작
for classification originally they were using and how it's not then then next we
원래 분류를 위해 그들이 사용하고 그 다음 다음 다음 아니에요 어떻게
actually want to fine tune this model for detection rate because this this
실제로 미세 조정이이 때문에 검출 율이 모델을 원하는
classification model was probably trained on image that 4,000 classes but
분류 모델은 아마 이미지에 대한 교육을하였습니다 4000 클래스 만
your detection dataset has a different number of classes in the image that
하여 검출 데이터 세트는 이미지 클래스의 다른 번호를 갖는다
extra little bit different so you still run this you still train this network
당신은 여전히​​이 실행되도록 여전히이 네트워크를 훈련 여분 조금 다른
for classification
분류
you have to add a couple new layers at the end to deal with your classes and to
당신은 당신의 클래스를하고 처리하는 말에 몇 새 레이어를 추가해야
help you deal with slightly different statistics of your image data so here
그렇게 여기에 이​​미지 데이터의 약간 다른 통계 처리에 도움
you're just doing classification still but you're not running on hold images
당신은 여전히​​ 분류를하고있어하지만 당신은 보류 이미지에서 실행하지 않는
you're running out on positive and negative regions of your images from
당신은에서 이미지의 긍정적이고 부정적인 지역에 밖으로 실행하고
your detection dataset right so you initially as a new layer and you and you
당신의 감지 데이터 세트 바로 처음에 새 레이어로 그래서 당신과 당신
train this thing again for your day is that
하루는 것입니다 다시이 일을 양성
next we actually want to casualties features two desks so for every
다음 우리가 실제로 사고에 할 모든에 대한 그래서 두 개의 책상을 갖추고 있습니다
engineered in your data that you run selective search you run that image you
당신이 선택 검색을 실행하는 데이터에 조작 된 해당 이미지를 실행
extract those regions you were down here on the CNN and you cash those features
당신이 아래로 여기 CNN에 있었다 그 영역을 추출하고 그 기능을 현금으로
to desk and something important for this step is to have a large hard drive the
책상이 단계에 대한 중요한 뭔가가 큰 하드 드라이브를하는 것입니다에
passcode they decided not too big maybe order a couple tens of thousands of
암호는 어쩌면 수천의 몇 수십 주문 너무 큰하지 않기로 결정
images but extracting these features actually takes hundreds of gigabytes so
이미지하지만 이러한 기능을 추출 실제로 그렇게 수백 기가 바이트 소요
that's not so great and then next we have this we want to train RSP arms to
그건 그리 중대하고 다음 우리는 우리가 RSP의 팔을 훈련 할이 있습니다
actually be able to classify different are different classes based on these
이러한 사실에 기초하여 상이한 다른 클래스로 분류 할 수
features so here we want to run a bunch of we want to change a bunch of
기능은 여기에, 그래서 우리는 우리의 무리를 변경할의 무리를 실행하려면
different binary as PM's to classify image regions as to whether or not they
PM의 서로 다른 바이너리에로 이미지 영역을 분류 할 것인지 여부를 그들이
contain or don't contain that that one object to this goes back to a question a
포함하거나 해당 하나의 오브젝트 질문 (A)에 다시가는 것을 포함하지 않는다
little bit ago that sometimes you actually might wanna how one region have
전 약간은 때때로 당신은 실제로 한 지역이 얼마나 싶어 있습니다
multiple positive be able to output YES on multiple classes for the same image
여러 긍정적는 같은 이미지를 여러 클래스에 출력 YES로 수
region and one way that they do that is just my training separate binary SVM
그들이 그 그냥 내 훈련 별도의 이진 SVM입니다 않는 영역과 하나의 방법
speech class right so then this is sort of an offline process they just used the
음성 클래스는 바로 그래서 다음이 그들은 단지를 사용하여 오프라인 프로세스의 일종이다
best p.m. so you have these features these are maybe those are positive
이 어쩌면 그들이다 긍정적 인 당신이이 기능을 가지고 있도록 최선 오후
samples for a countess yeah it doesn't make any sense right but you get the
백작에 대한 샘플은 그래 그것은 어떤 의미의 권리를하지 않습니다하지만 당신은 얻을
idea rate you have these different imagery you have these different image
생각의 속도 당신은 당신이 다른 이미지를 서로 다른 이미지를 가지고있다
regions you have these features that you save to disk for those regions and then
영역은 당신이 다음 해당 지역과의 디스크에 저장이 기능을 가지고 있습니다
you divide them into positive and negative samples for each for each class
각 클래스에 대한 각각의 양극과 음극 샘플로 분할
and you just train these these binary SVM you do this you do this the same
방금이 이러한 이진 SVM 훈련이 작업을 수행이에게 동일한 작업을 수행
thing for dog and you just do this for every class near to decide right now
개를위한 것이나, 당신은 단지 근처 지금 결정하는 모든 클래스에 대해이 작업을 수행
there's another stop right if so then there's this idea of Cox regression so
그럼 이렇게 콕스 회귀의이 아이디어가 있다면 다른 정지 권리가있다
sometimes you region proposals aren't perfect so what we actually want to do
때로는 지역의 제안은 우리가 실제로 무엇을 원하는 그렇게 완벽하지
is be able to regress from from his cast features to a correction on to the
받는 사람에 교정에 그의 캐스트 기능에서에서 퇴보 할 수있다
region proposal and that correction has this kind of funny premise rise
지역 제안하고 보정 재미 전제 상승의이 종류가 있습니다
normalize representation the country details about in the paper but kind of
종이뿐만 종류의에 대한 표현을 국가의 세부 사항을 정상화
intuition is that maybe for this for this for this region proposal it was
직관은 어쩌면이이이 지역의 제안에 대해 그것이이다
pretty good we don't really need to make any any corrections but maybe this one
꽤 좋은 우리가 정말 어떤 어떤 수정하지만 어쩌면이 일을 할 필요가 없습니다
in the middle that proposal was too far to the left it should be like the crib
제안은 너무 멀리 왼쪽에있는 것을 중간에 그것은 침대처럼한다
cracked ground truth as a little bit to the right we want to regress to this
우리는 이것에 회귀 할 오른쪽으로 조금으로 금이 지상의 진실
correction factor that actually tell us that we need to shift a little bit to
보정 계수 실제로 우리가 조금 이동해야한다는 것을 우리에게 말해 그
the right or maybe this guy is a little bit too wide
오른쪽 또는 어쩌면이 사람은 조금 너무 넓
they didn't lose too much of the stuff outside the cat so we want to regress to
우리가 퇴보 할 수 있도록 그들은 고양이 이외의 물건을 너무 많이 잃지 않았다
this correction factor that tells us we need to shrink
우리에게이 보정 계수 우리는 축소해야
region proposal a little bit so again this is just let me just do linear
지역의 제안은 조금 그래서 다시는 날 그냥 선형을 수행 할 수있다
regression which you can but you know from 229 you have these these features
당신은 그러나 당신이 229에서 알 수 회귀 이러한에게 이러한 기능을 가지고 있습니다
you have these targets you you just ran linear regression i SAT so before we
그냥 내가 우리 전에 그렇게 SAT 선형 회귀를 실행하면 이러한 목표를 가지고
look at the results we should talk to talk a little bit about the different
우리는 다른에 대해 조금 이야기를 이야기해야 결과를 보면
datasets the people used for detection there's kind of three that you'll see in
데이터 세트 검출에 사용되는 사람들이 당신이 볼 세 가지의 종류가있다
practice one as the Pascal the OC dataset it was pretty important I think
파스칼과 같은 연습 하나는 OC 데이터 세트는 내가 생각하는 매우 중요
in the earlier to thousands but now it's a little bit small this one's about 20
수천 이전에 있지만, 지금은 조금 작다이 하나의 약 20
classes and about 20,000 images and hence have about two objects percentage
클래스에 따라서 약 20,000 이미지와는 약 2 개체의 비율이
so because this is a relatively small ish dataset you'll see a lot of
이 상대적으로 작은 틱 데이터 세트가 너무 때문에 당신을 많이 볼 수 있습니다
detection papers work on this just goes it's easier to handle but there's also
검출 논문이에 그냥 처리하기 쉽게가는 일뿐만 아니라, 거기에
an image that detection dataset image that runs a whole bunch of challenges as
문제의 전체 무리로 실행 이미지가 검출 데이터 세트 이미지
you've probably seen by now we saw a classification we sought localisation
당신은 아마 우리가 현지화 노력 분류를 보았다 지금까지 본 적이
there's also an image that detection challenge but protection there's only
검출 도전하지만 보호 만이 있다는 이미지도있다
two hundred classes not the thousand from classification but it's it's very
이백 클래스하지 분류에서 천 그러나 그것은 매우의의
big almost half a million images so you don't see as many papers work on it just
당신은 많은 논문이 작업이 표시되지 않도록 큰 거의 50 만 이미지 만
cuz it's kind of annoying to handle but there's only about 100 per image and
이 처리 할 종류의 짜증나지만 이미지 당 약 100 거기에 사촌과
then more weeks more recently there's this one from Microsoft called Coco
다음 주 이상은 최근 코코라는 Microsoft에서 제공하는이 일이있다
which has fewer classes images but actually has a lot more objects
이는 적은 수의 클래스 이미지를 가지고 있지만 실제로는 더 많은 개체가
percentage so people like to work I'm not now has more interesting right
사람들이 아니에요 일을 같은 비율은 더욱 흥미있는 권리가있다
there's also this this when you're talking about detection there's this
당신이 거기 검출에 대해 얘기하고이이 또한있다
funny evaluation metric we use called mean average precision and early wanna
재미 평가 메트릭은 우리가 평균 평균 정밀도와 초기 싶어라고 사용하십시오
get too much into the details like what you really need to know is that it's a
얻을 당신은 정말 알아야 할 사항 등 세부 사항에 너무 많이는 점입니다
number between 0 and hundreds and hundreds good and it
0 수백 좋은 수백과 사이의 수
and it also I mean the kind of the intuition is that it's you want to have
그리고 그것은 또한 내가 직관의 종류의 IT 당신이하려는 의미
the right you wanna have true positives get high scores and you also have to
오른쪽 당신 싶어 사실이 긍정적 높은 점수를 얻을 당신은 또한에있다가
have some threshold that your boxes you produced need to be within some
당신의 상자가 일부 내에 할 필요가 생산 몇 가지 한계를 가지고
threshold of a crack box and you can usually this that threshold this point
균열 상자의 임계 값을 수행 할 수 있습니다 보통이 그 임계 값이 점
by an intersection of a union but you'll see different challenges you slightly
노조 만의 교차에 의해 당신은 당신이 약간 다른 문제를 볼 수 있습니다
different things for thats right so let's now that we understand the data
그게 전부 다른 일이 바로 지금 우리가 데이터를 이해하자
sets on the elevation of us via our CNN did right so this is on the past two
우리의 CNN을 통해 우리의 높이에 설정하는 것은 바로 그래서이 지난 2에 않았다
versions of the Pascal Davis at like I said it's smaller as you'll see a lot of
등의 파스칼 데이비스의 버전 난 당신을 많이 볼 수 있습니다로 작은 말했습니다
results on this there's different versions one in 2007 2010 you often see
이에 대한 결과를 다른 버전을 자주 볼 2007, 2010 년을 거기에
people use those just because the test is publicly available so it's easy to
사람들은 테스트가 공개되어해서 사람들을 사용 그래서 쉽게
evaluate
평가
yeah but so in this this deformable parts model that we saw from 2011 from
그래,하지만 우리가에서 2011 년부터 본이이 변형 부품 모델
couple slides ago is getting twenty about 30 on average precision there's
커플 슬라이드는 전 약 30 평균 정밀도에있다 스무을 받고있다
this other method called region let's from 2013 that was sort of the state of
지역이라는 다른 방법은 국가의 종류이었다 2013에서하자
the art that I could find right before deep learning but it's it's sort of a
내가 바로 깊은 학습을하기 전에하지만 그것 뿐이다 찾을 수있는 예술은 일종의이다
similar flavor you have these features in its class players on top of teachers
비슷한 맛 당신은 교사의 상단에 동급 플레이어에서 이러한 기능을 가지고 있습니다
and our CNN is this pretty simple thing we just saw and actually jump and
우리의 CNN 우리가 방금 본이 꽤 간단한 일이 실제로 점프
actually improves the performance quite a lot so the first thing the Seas we had
실제로 성능에게 우리가 가진 가장 먼저 바다, 그래서 꽤 많이 향상
a big improvement when we just switch this pretty simple framework using CNN's
우리가 사용하는 CNN의이 매우 간단한 프레임 워크를 전환 큰 개선
and actually this this result here is without the bounding box repressions
여기에 실제로이 결과는 경계 상자의 억압없이
this is only using the region proposals on ESPN's actually if you include this
이 포함되어있는 경우에만 실제로 ESPN의 영역에 제안을 사용
additional bonding proposal stop it actually helps quite a bet another fun
추가로 결합 제안은 실제로 또 다른 재미 꽤 내기를하는 데 도움이 중지
thing to note is that if you take our CNN and you do everything the same
주의해야 할 것은 당신이 우리의 CNN을 가지고 있다면 당신은 모든 것을에게 같은 행동을 할 것입니다
except used eg 16 instead of Alex net you get another pretty big boost in
사용 예 (16) 대신 알렉스 그물을 제외한 다른 꽤 큰 부스트에서 얻을
performance so this is kind of similar to what we've seen before that just
성능은 그래서 이것은 종류의 우리가 그 바로 전에 보았던 것과 비슷한입니다
using these more powerful features tends to help a lot of different tasks right
바로 다른 작업을 많이하는 데 도움이 더 강력한 기능을 경향 사용
this is really good right we've we've done like a huge improvement on
이것은 우리가 우리가에 큰 개선을 같이했던 한 정말 좋은 권리
detection compared to 2013 that's amazing but our CNN is not perfect it
검출 놀라운 2013에 비해 그러나 우리의 CNN은 완벽하지 않습니다
has some problems right so it's pretty slow its test time right we saw that we
바로 그래서 꽤 우리가 우리 것을보고 그 시험 시간을 오른쪽으로 느린 몇 가지 문제가있다
have maybe two thousand regions means to evaluate our CNN for each region that's
아마 이천 지역을하면의 각 지역에 대한 우리의 CNN을 평가하는 것을 의미한다
kinda slow we also have this this slightly subtle problem where r SVM
좀 느린 우리는이 곳이 약간 미묘한 문제가 r에 SVM
regression those were sort of trained off-line using likely best p.m.
사람들은 일종의 가능성이 가장 오후를 사용하여 오프라인 교육을 받았습니다 회귀
and linear regression actually the weights of our of our CNN didn't really
그리고 실제로 무게 선형 회귀 우리의 우리의 CNN은 정말하지 않았다의
have the chance to update in response to what those parts of of a network of
갱신에 응답 할 기회를 갖고 것의 네트워크의 해당 부분
those objectives wanted to do and we also had this kind of complicated
그 목적은하고 싶었던 우리는 또한 복잡한 이런 종류의했다
training pipeline that was a bit of a mess so to fix these problems a year
혼란의 비트를했다 훈련 파이프 라인은 그래서 년 이러한 문제를 해결하기 위해
later we have this thing called fast our CNN so fast our CNN it was presented
나중에 우리가 제시 한 빨리 우리의 CNN이 너무 빨리 우리의 CNN이라이 일이
pretty recently in ICC be just in December but the idea is really simple
꽤 최근 ICC 년 12 월에 바로 할 수 있지만, 아이디어는 정말 간단합니다
we're just gonna swap the order of extracting regions and running the CNN
우리는 CNN을 영역을 추출하고 실행의 순서 만 거 스왑이야
this is kind of a kind of related to the sliding window idea we saw with
이것은 우리가 본 슬라이딩 윈도우 아이디어에 관련의 종류의 종류
over-the-top so here the pipeline that test time looks kinda similar we have
이상 - 더 - 상단 그래서 여기에 테스트 시간은 우리가 좀 비슷한 모양의 파이프 라인
this input image we're gonna not we're going to take this high-resolution input
우리가하지거야이 입력 이미지를 우리는 고해상도 입력을거야
image and run it through the convolutional layers of our network and
이미지와 우리의 네트워크의 길쌈 레이어를 통해 그것을 실행하고
now we're gonna get this high-resolution convolutional feature map and now our
지금 우린 지금이 고해상도 길쌈 기능지도를 얻고있어 우리의
region proposals were gonna extracts directly features for those region
지역의 제안은 직접 그 지역의 특징 거 추출했다
proposals from this convolutional feature map using this thing called ROI
투자 수익 (ROI)라는이 일을 사용하여이 길쌈 기능지도에서 제안
pooling and then the region's
풀링하고 지역의
the features for these the compositional features for those regions will be fed
그 지역에 대한이 조성 기능에 대한 기능은 공급한다
into our fully connected layers and will again have a classification had a
우리의 완전히 연결 층으로 다시 것입니다 분류가 가진
regression had like we saw before so this is really cool it's it's pretty
그래서 이것은 정말 꽤입니다의 냉각되기 전에 우리가 본 것처럼 회귀했다
great it solves a lot of the problems that we just saw with our CNN so our CNN
큰 우리가 너무 우리의 CNN 우리의 CNN과 본 많은 문제를 해결
is really slow at US time we solve this problem by just sharing this this
우리가이이를 공유함으로써이 문제를 해결 US 시간에 정말 느리다
computation of convolutional features across the region proposals are see our
지역의 제안에 걸쳐 길쌈 기능의 계산은 참조하는 우리의
CNN also have these problems at training time where we had this this message
CNN은 또한 우리가이 메시지를 가지고 교육 시간에 이러한 문제가
training pipeline we had this this problem where we're training different
교육 파이프 라인 우리는 우리가 다른 훈련하고이이 문제를 가지고 있었다
parts of the network separately and the solution is pretty simple we just you
별도로 네트워크 용액 부분 우리 그냥 매우 간단
know training all together all at once
알고 한 번에 모두 함께 훈련
don't don't have this complicated pipeline which we can actually do it now
우리가 실제로 지금 할 수있는이 복잡한 파이프 라인이없는하지 않습니다
that we have this this pretty nice function from inputs to outputs right as
우리는이는 바로 출력하는 입력에서이 꽤 좋은 기능을 가지고
you can see that are so that fast our CNN actually solves quite a lot of the
당신은 그래서 빨리 우리의 CNN이 실제로 꽤 많이 해결되어 있는지 볼 수 있습니다
problems that we saw with our CNN sort of them with a really interesting
우리가 정말 흥미로 우리의 CNN 정렬 보았다 문제
technical bit in fast our CNN was this problem of our way region of interest
빨리 우리의 CNN 기술적 비트는 관심의 길 영역이 문제였다
pooling so the idea is that we have this input image that's probably high
아이디어 있도록 풀링 우리가 아마 고의이 입력 이미지를 가지고있다
resolution and we have this region proposal that's becoming
해상도와 우리는되고있어이 지역의 제안을
elective surgery boxes or something like that and we can put this region this
선택 과목 수술 상자 또는 뭔가처럼 우리는이 지역이을 넣을 수 있습니다
high resolution image through our convolutional and pooling layers just
우리의 길쌈 및 풀링 층 단지를 통해 높은 해상도 이미지
fine because those are sort of scale-invariant they're still up two
잘 그들이가 여전히이있어 규모 불변의 일종이다 그 때문에
different sizes of inputs but now the problem is that the fully connected
다른 입력의 크기 그러나 지금 문제가 완전히 연결이다
layers from our pre train network are expecting these pretty low res con
우리의 전 열차 네트워크의 층이 매우 낮은 입술 죄수를 기대하고있다
features whereas these features from the whole image are high res so now we solve
전체 이미지에서 이러한 기능 반면 기능은 지금 우리가 해결 고해상도있다
this problem in a pretty straightforward way so given this region proposal we're
아주 간단한 방법으로이 문제는 우리가있어이 지역의 제안을 부여
gonna projected onto it sort of the special part of that comment feature
야는에 그 댓글 기능의 특수 부품의 종류 전망
volume now we're going to divide that Khan future vol into a little grid right
볼륨 이제 우리는 작은 격자 오른쪽에 그 칸 미래의 부피를 나눌거야
divide that thing into this hiw grid that downstream layers are expecting and
이 HIW 계통에 그 일을 분할 하류 층이 기대하고 있고
we do Macs pulling within each of those grid cells so now we've seen now we have
우리는 지금 우리가 우리가 본 적이 그래서 지금 그 그리드의 각 셀 내에서 당겨 맥을
this pretty simple strategy we've taken this region proposal and we've shared
이 아주 간단한 전략 우리는이 지역의 제안을 찍은 우리가 공유 한
compilation features extracted this excites output for that region for that
편집 기능이 그에 대한 그 지역의 출력을 자극 추출
for that region proposal writes this is basically just swapping the order of
해당 지역의 제안이 기본적으로 단지의 순서를 교환한다 기록
convolution and warping and cropping that's one way to think about it and
하나의 방법 회선 및 휨 및 자르기 그것에 대해 생각하고
also this is a pretty nice operation because since this thing is basically
이 것은 기본적으로부터 때문에이 꽤 좋은 동작이다
just max pulling and we know how to back propagate through max pulling you can
다만 최대는 당기 우리는 당겨 최대를 통해 수행 할 수 있습니다 전파 백업하는 방법을 알고
back propagate through these are these are region of interest pulling there's
다시이이 통해이 거기에 당기는 관심의 영역이 전파
just fine and that's what really allows us to train this whole thing in a joint
잘하고 정말 관절에이 모든 일을 훈련하는 우리를 할 수 있습니다 무엇
way rights let's see some results and these are actually pretty cool pretty
방법 권한의 일부 결과를 볼 수 있도록 이러한 꽤 꽤 멋진
amazing great so for training time are CNN it had this complicated pipeline
훈련 시간이 너무 놀라운 큰는 CNN입니다 그것은이 복잡한 파이프 라인을 가지고 있었다
would save all the stuff that desk where to do all this stuff independently and
책상 곳이 모든 물건을 독립적으로 수행하는 모든 물건을 절약 할 수 및
even on that pretty small Pascale Denis at it took eighty four hours to train
심지어 아주 작은 파스칼 데니스에이 훈련 팔십사시간 걸렸다에서
passed our CNN is much faster you can train and a at as far as test time in LR
우리의 CNN이 LR의 테스트 시간으로 멀리에서 훨씬 더 빨리 당신이 훈련 할 수있다 및 전달
CNN is pretty slow because again we're running these independent forward passes
다시 우리는 이러한 독립적 인 전진을 실행하는 것은 전달하기 때문에 CNN은 매우 느립니다
at the CNN for each region proposal whereas for fast our CNN where we can
반면 빠른 우리의 CNN 각 지역의 제안에 대한 CNN의 경우 우리가 할 수있는
sort of share the computation between different region proposals and get this
종류의 다른 지역 제안의 계산을 공유하고이를 얻을 수
gigantic speed up a test I'm a hundred and forty-six that's great amazing and
테스트 거대한 속도까지 난 백이다 마흔여섯 큰 놀랍고
in fact in terms of performance I mean it does a little bit better it's not a
성능면 내 말에 사실은 그것은 조금 더 나은 아니다 않는다
drastic difference in performance but this could probably be attributed to
이 아마에 기인 할 수 있지만 성능에 급격한 차이
this fine tuning property that
이 미세 조정 속성이
past our CNN you can actually find you in all parts of the convolutional
우리의 CNN 과거 실제로 길쌈의 모든 부분이 당신을 찾을 수 있습니다
network jointly to help with these ALPA tasks and that's probably why you see a
이 ALPA 작업에 도움이 공동으로 네트워크와 당신이 볼 이유는 아마
bit of an increase here right so this is great right what's what could possibly
증가의 비트가 바로 여기 그래서 이것은 무엇을 가능하게 할 수 무슨 큰 권리
be wrong with fast our CNN and its looks amazing
놀라운 우리의 CNN과 외모 빠른 잘못 될
the big problem is that these tests I'm speeds don't include region proposals
큰 문제는 이러한 테스트 나는 속도는 지역의 제안을 포함하지 않는거야이다
right so now fast our CNN the so good that actually the bottleneck is
바로 지금 실제로 병목이라는 정말 좋은 우리의 CNN을 빨리
computing region proposals that's pretty cool so once you factor in the speed of
의 속도는 고려 번, 그래서 꽤 멋진 지역의 제안을 계산
computer actually computing these region proposals on CPU you can see that a lot
컴퓨터가 실제로 당신이 많은 것을 볼 수 있습니다 CPU에이 지역의 제안을 계산
of our speed benefits disappear right only 25 x faster and we kind of lost
우리의 속도의 장점은 빠른 바로 25 X 사라 우리 종류의 손실의
that beautiful hundred speed-up also now because it takes me two seconds Tehran
그 아름다운 백 속도 업도 지금은 나 이초에게이란이 걸리기 때문에
actually pretty magenta and you can't really use this real-time it still kinda
실제로 꽤 마젠타 그리고 당신이 정말로 좀 여전히이 실시간으로 사용할 수 없습니다
off-line processing thing right so the solution of this should be pretty
오프라인 처리 것은 바로 그래서 이것의 해결책은 꽤해야한다
obvious rate we are all you're already using a convolutional network for
우리 모두가 이미 컨볼 루션 네트워크를 사용하는 명백한 속도
regression using it for classification why not use it for a reason proposals to
분류를 사용하여 회귀 이유에 대한 이유 제안을 위해 그것을 사용하지
write should work may be kind of crazy so that's that's a paper anyone want to
즉 그, 그래서 종류의 미친 수 있습니다 작동합니다 작성하는 종이 사람이 원하는이다
guess the name yes it's faster our CNN
이름이 예는 빠르게 우리의 CNN을 것 같아요
yes they were they were really creative here right but the idea is pretty simple
예 그들은 여기 정말 창조적했다 있었다하지만 아이디어는 매우 간단하다
right where some from fast our CNN where are you taking our input image and where
바로 여기서 당신은 우리의 입력 이미지를 복용하는 경우 빠른 우리의 CNN에서 일부 어디
computing these big convolutional feature maps over the entire input image
전체 입력 화상 위에 빅 컨벌루션 피쳐 맵을 계산
so that instead of using some external method to compute region proposals they
그래서 그 대신 일부 외부 방법을 사용하는 지역의 제안을 계산하는 그들
add this little thing called the region proposal network that looks directly at
직접 보이는 지역 제안 네트워크라는이 작은 일을 추가
these looks at these last their compositional features as able to
이들의 이러한 외모에 수 그들의 조성 기능을 지속
produce region proposals directly from that competition will feature map and
지도 기능을합니다 그 경쟁에서 직접 지역의 제안을 생산하고
then once you have region proposals you just do the same thing as fast our CNN
이 지역의 제안을 일단 당신은 그냥 빨리 우리의 CNN을 같은 일을
you use this ROI pooling and I'll be upstream stop is the same as fast or CNN
이 ROI 풀링을 사용하고 난 상류 정지가 빠르거나 CNN과 동일 수 있습니다
so really about the novel bit here is this region proposal network it's it's
그래서 여기 정말에 대한 새로운 비트는 그것의이 지역 제안 네트워크는 그것의이다
really cool right we're doing the whole thing and one giant competition at work
정말 멋진 바로 우리가 모든 일을하고있는 직장에서 하나의 거대한 경쟁
right so the way this region proposal network works is that were sort of we
옳았다이이 지역 제안 네트워크가 작동하는 방식은 우리 종류의
receive as input this competition will feature map this may be coming out of
이 매핑 기능을합니다이 경쟁에서 나오는 수의 입력으로받을
the last layer of our convolutional features and we're going to add you like
마지막으로 우리의 길쌈 기능 층과 우리는 당신이 좋아하는 추가 할거야
like most things are recent post on that worked as a convolutional network right
대부분의 물건이있는 것처럼 그에 최근 포스트는 컨볼 루션 네트워크를 오른쪽으로 일했다
so actually this is a typo this is a free by freak on that right so we have a
그래서 실제로 우리가이 있도록 그 권리에 괴물에 의해이 무료 인 오타입니다
sort of a sliding window approach over our convolutional feature map but
우리의 길쌈 기능지도를 통해 슬라이딩 윈도우 방식의 종류 만
sliding sliding window is just a convolution rate so we just have a three
슬라이딩 창 슬라이딩 그래서 우리는 단지 세 가지가 단지 회선 속도입니다
by three convolution on top of this feature map and then we have this this
셋이 기능지도의 상단에 컨볼 루션 다음으로 우리는 이것을 가지고
peculiar struck this familiar to head structure inside the region proposal
독특한이 지역 제안 내부 헤드 구조에이 익숙에게 공격
network where we're doing classification we're here we just want to say whether
우리가 분류하고있는 네트워크 우리는 우리가인지 말하고 싶은 여기
or not it's an object and also regression to regress from this sort of
여부는 객체이고 또한 이런 종류의에서 회귀하는 회귀
position on to an actual pridgen proposal so the idea is that the
실제 pridgen 제안에에 위치가 너무 생각이 그
position of the sliding window relative to the feature map sort of tells us
기능지도에 슬라이딩 윈도우 상대의 위치는 종류의 우리에게 알려줍니다
where we are in the image and then these regression outputs sort of give us
우리는 이미지에 다음이 회귀 일종의 출력 곳의 우리에게
corrections on top of this this position in the feature map but actually they
기능 맵이이 위치의 상단에 수정하지만 실제로
make it a little bit more complicated than that so instead of addressing
그것은 조금 더보다 복잡한 그래서 대신 주소 확인
directly from this position in the convolution will feature map they have
회선이 위치가지도 기능을합니다에서 직접 자신이 갖고
this notion of these different anchor boxes you can imagine taking these
당신이 복용 상상할 수있는 서로 다른 앵커 상자의이 개념
different sized and shaped banker boxes and sort of pasting them in the original
다른 크기와 모양의 은행 상자 원래대로 붙여 넣기의 종류
image at the point of the image corresponding to this point in the
이 시점에 대응하는 화상의 시점 화상
feature map right leg and fast RCMP were projecting forward from the image into
기능지도 오른쪽 다리와 빠른 RCMP는로 이미지에서 앞으로 돌출 된
the feature map now we're doing the opposite we're projecting from the
이 기능지도 이제 우리는 우리가 돌​​출하고 반대를하고있는
feature map back into the image for these boxes so then for each of these
기능지도 다시이 상자에 대한 이미지로 그렇게 한 다음 이들 각각에 대한
anchor boxes they use sort of an convolutional anchor boxes may use the
앵커 상자 그들은을 사용할 수있는 길쌈 앵커 상자의 종류를 사용
same ones at every position in the image and they for each of these anchor boxes
이 앵커 박스의 각각에 대한 모든 이미지의 위치와 그들이에서 동일합니다
they produce score as to whether or not that anchor box corresponds to an object
이들은 그 앵커 상자 객체에 해당하는지 여부에 대한 점수를 생성
and they also produce for regression coordinates that's incorrect that anger
그들은 또한 분노가 잘못의 회귀 좌표에 대한 생산
box in similar ways that we saw before and now this region proposal network you
우리가 전에 보았던 유사한 방식으로 상자와 지금이 지역의 제안 네트워크 당신에게
can just trained to try to predict it's sort of a high-class agnostic object
그냥 높은 수준의 불가지론 객체의 일종의 예측하려고하는 훈련을 할 수 있습니다
detector so faster our CNN in the original paper they train this thing and
원래 논문에서 이렇게 빨리 우리의 CNN 검출기 그들은이 일을 훈련하고
kind of a funny way where first they train read a proposal not work then they
그들이 제안을 읽는 훈련을 먼저 재미있는 방법의 종류를 잘 작성하지 다음 작업들이
train passed our CNN then they do some magic to merge together and at the end
다음 우리의 CNN을 통과 기차 그들은 함께하고 마지막에 병합하는 마법을
of the day they have one network that produces everything so this this is a
이 이것은 그래서 오늘의 그들은 모든 것을 생성 한 네트워크를 가지고
little bit messy but individual paper they describe this thing but since then
조금 지저분하지만 개별 종이는이 일을 설명하지만, 그 이후
they've had some unpublished work where they actually just change the whole
그들은 실제로 단지 전체를 변경 일부 미 출판 일을 했어
thing jointly where they're sort of have one big network where you have an image
그들은 종류의 이미지를 가지고 하나의 큰 네트워크를 가지고있어 공동으로 일
coming in you have this in inside the region proposal network you have a
당신이 지역의 제안서 네트워크 내에서 이것을에 가지고 오는을 설치해야
classification lost to classify whether each region proposal is or is not an
분류는 각 지역의 제안이 있거나인지 여부를 분류하는 손실
object you have these bounding box regressions inside the region proposal
당신은이 지역의 제안 안에 이러한 경계 상자의 회귀가 객체
not work on top of your competition anchors and then from fast then we do
하지 빨리 우리가 할에서 다음 대회 앵커의 상단에 작동
our life pooling and do this fast our CNN trek and then at the end of the
우리의 삶 풀링의 끝에서 다음이 빠른 우리의 CNN 여행을하고와
network we have this classification lost to say which class that is and this
네트워크 우리는이 분류는 그 어느 클래스 말을 잃었다가이
regression lost to correct a correction on top of the region proposal so this is
회귀 때문에이이 지역 제안의 상단에 수정을 해결하기 위해 손실
this big thing is just one big network with four losses yeah
이 큰 것은 그래 네 손실을 단지 하나의 큰 네트워크입니다
so the proposal and repression coordinates are produced by a three by
그래서 제안과 억압 좌표는 세에 의해 생산된다
three three by three and an apparent one-by-one convolutions often feature
세 가지로 삼 세와 명백한 하나씩 회선 종종 있습니다
map right so the idea is that we're looking at these different anchor boxes
지도 오른쪽 그래서 아이디어는 우리가 서로 다른 앵커 상자에서 찾고 있다는 점이다
of different positions and scales but we're actually looking at the same
다른 위치와 비늘 만의 우리는 실제로 같은보고있는
position in the feature map to classify those different banker boxes but you
기능 맵의 위치는 그 다른 은행 상자를 분류하지만합니다
have different you learn different weights for the different anchors I
당신은 다른 앵커에 대해 서로 다른 가중치를 다른 학습 한 I
think it's mostly empirical right so the three by the idea is just you want to
아이디어에 의해 세 당신이 원하는, 그래서 그것은 주로 경험적 바로 생각
have a little bit of nonlinearity you could imagine just doing sort of a
비선형의 약간을 가지고 당신은 단지 종류의 일을 상상할 수
direct one-by-one convolution directly off the feature maps but I think they
직접 나는 그들이 생각하지만, 기능 맵 오프 직접 하나씩 회선
don't discuss this in the paper but I'm guessing just a three by three times to
신문에서이 문제를 논의하지 않습니다하지만 난에 단지 3 × 3 회 같은데요
work a bit better but there's no like really deep reason why you why you do
더 조금 작동하지만 당신은 왜 당신이 왜 같은 정말 깊은 이유가 없습니다
that you could be more could be less that could be a bigger colonel is just
적은 수 더있을 수 있다는 것을 더 큰 대령은 그냥 수
sort of you have this little competition at work with two heads that's the main
당신의 종류는 메인의 두 개의 머리를 가진 직장이 작은 경쟁이
point and your questions
포인트 및 질문
yeah I understand because
그래 나는 때문에 이해
corresponds to the whole image
전체 이미지에 대응
the point is that we don't actually want to process the whole image you want to
요점은 우리가 실제로 원하는 전체 이미지를 처리​​하지 않는다는 것입니다
pick out some regions of the image to do more processing on but we need to choose
에 대한 처리를 할 수있는 이미지의 일부 지역을 선택하지만 우리는 선택해야
those regions somehow
어떻게 든 그 지역
yes that's basically the that's basically this idea of using external
예 즉, 그것은 기본적으로 기본적으로 외부 사용이 생각입니다
region proposals right so when you do that external region proposals you're
당신이 그 외부 지역의 제안을 수행 할 때 지역의 제안은 바로 그래서 당신은있어
sort of picking it first before you do the convolutions but it's just sort of a
종류의 당신이 회선을하기 전에 먼저 따기하지만 그것은 단지 종류의의
nice thing if you can do it all at once so it's like I'm illusions are kind of
난처럼 당신이 한 번에 모든 것을 할 수 있다면 좋은 점은, 그래서 그것은 환상이 가지입니다입니다
this general like really general processing processing but you can do to
정말 일반 가공 처리 등이 일반적으로하지만 당신은 할 수있는
the image you're kinda hoping that contributions are good enough for
당신이 좀 기여가 충분 것을 바라고 이미지
classification gonna aggression the types of information that you have in
분류 거 침략 당신이이 정보의 유형
those contributions is probably good enough for classifying regions as well
이러한 기여는 물론 지역을 분류하기위한 충분한 아마 좋은
so it's actually it's actually a computational savings because at the end
그래서 그것 때문에 끝에 실제로 계산 절감의 사실이다
of the day you end up using that same convolutional Peter map for everything
오늘의 당신은 모두를위한 동일한 길쌈 피터 맵을 사용하게
for the region proposals for the downstream classification for the dam
댐의 하류 분류 영역 제안서
downstream regression that's actually why you get the speed up here
여기에 속도를 얻을 왜 사실이다 하류 회귀
question yes we have this big network we train with four losses and now we can do
질문 그래, 우리는 우리가 네 손실 훈련이 큰 네트워크를 가지고 지금 우리가 할 수있는
object detection sort of all at once
모든 물체 감지 정렬 한 번에
pretty cool so if we look at results comparing the free our CNN's of various
정말 멋진 우리가 CNN의 다양한의 자유를 비교 결과를 보면, 그래서
velocities then we have original our CNN it took about 50 seconds a test time per
속도는 우리는 약 50 초 테스트 시간 당 걸렸다 원래 우리의 CNN이
image this is counting the region proposals this is counting running the
영상이이 실행중인 계산되는 영역의 제안을 기대하고있다
CNN separately for each region proposal that's pretty slow now passed our CNN we
CNN 별도로 꽤 느린 지금 전달 우리의 CNN있어 각 지역의 제안에 대한 우리
saw it was sort of bottleneck by the region proposal time but once we move to
우리가 이동하면 그것은 일종의 지역 제안 시간으로 병목되었지만 보았다
faster our CNN than those region proposals are basically coming for free
빨리 우리의 CNN을 그 지역의 제안보다 기본적으로 무료오고있다
since they're just the way we compute region proposals is just a tiny three my
그들은 단지 방법에 있기 때문에 우리는 지역의 제안을 계산은 작은 세 내
free time dilution and a couple one-by-one convolutions so they're very
자유 시간 희석과 몇 하나씩 회선들이있어, 그래서 매우
cheap to evaluate it sent a test times faster our CNN runs in the fifth of a
우리의 CNN이의 다섯 번째에서 실행이 빠른 테스트 시간을 보낼 평가 저렴
second a pretty high resolution image that's actually yeah
실제로의 두 번째 꽤 높은 해상도 이미지 그래
well I mean you're not one of the ideas behind zero padding as you're hoping not
잘 난 당신이하지 기대하는대로 제로 패딩 뒤에 아이디어 중 하나를하지 않은 의미
too far away information from the edges so I think maybe you might have a
가장자리에서 너무 멀리 떨어져 정보는 그래서 당신이있을 수 있습니다 어쩌면 생각
problem with if you didn't do the zero padding and maybe more problem but I
당신이 제로 패딩을하지 않은 경우에 문제가 어쩌면 더 문제지만
mean as we sort of discussed before and the fact that you're adding that zero
우리는 일종의 전에 논의하고 제로 것을 추가하는 사실로 의미
padding might affect the statistics of those features so it could maybe be a
그것은 어쩌면이 될 수 있도록 패딩은 이러한 기능의 통계에 영향을 미칠 수
bit of a problem but in practice it seems to work just fine but actually
문제의 비트는하지만 실제로는 잘 작동하는 것 같다 실제로
about yeah that that's an analysis of where do we have a failure cases where
대한 그래 우리가 실패의 경우 어디에 있습니까 곳의 분석이다 그
do we get things wrong as a really important process when you develop new
새를 개발할 때 우리는 정말 중요한 과정으로 잘못된 일을받을 수 있나요
algorithms and I can give you insight into what might make things better
알고리즘과 나는 당신에게 더 나은 일을 할 수 있습니다 무엇에 대한 통찰력을 제공 할 수 있습니다
yeah yeah yeah
그래 그래
so maybe it might help but it's actually kinda hard to the next to do that
그래서 어쩌면 도움이 될 수 있지만, 그렇게 할 다음에 좀 어려운 사실이다
experiment because the data sets are different right because when you when
실험 데이터 세트가 다른 맞아 때문에 때 때를 때문에
you were kind of classification dataset like image now that's one thing but then
당신은 한 가지입니다하지만 지금 이미지와 같은 분류 데이터 세트의 종류이었다
when you work on detection it's this other data set and I haven't liked you
당신이 검출 작업을 할 때이 다른 데이터 세트 그리고 내가 당신을 좋아하지 않은
could imagine trying to classify the detection images based on what objects
어떤 객체에 기초하여 상기 검출 된 이미지를 분류하려고 상상할 수
are present but I haven't really seen any really good comparisons that try to
존재하지만 난 정말하려고하는 정말 좋은 비교를 보지 못했다
study that apparently but I mean that the experiment on your project
연구 분명하지만 내 말은 그 해당 프로젝트의 실험
yeah that's a very good question so then you have this problem with our way
그래 그건 아주 좋은 질문이 너무 그럼 당신은 우리의 방법이 문제가
pooling right because of the way that the ROI pooling work as well as by
하여 투자 수익 (ROI) 풀링 작업 그뿐만 아니라 오른쪽 방식 때문에 풀링
dividing that thing into the sixth grade and doing max pulling once you do
6 학년으로 그 일을 분할하고 당신이 한 번 당겨 최대 일
rotations it's actually kind of difficult there's this really cool paper
회전 실제로 가지 어려움이 정말 멋진 종이 거기에 있어요
from deep mind in the last over the summer called spatial transformer
공간 변압기라는 여름 동안 마지막에 깊은 마음에서
networks that actually introduces a really cool way to solve this problem in
실제로 정말 멋진 방법을 소개 네트워크는이 문제를 해결하기 위해
the idea is that instead of doing ROI pooling we're gonna do by linear
아이디어는 대신 ROI 풀링을하는 우리가 직선에 의해 야 할 것이다
interpolation kinda like you might be used for textures and graphics so once
좀 당신 같은 보간 ​​그래서 한 번 질감과 그래픽을 사용할 수 있습니다
you do by linear interpolation than you actually can do maybe these these crazy
실제로 아마이이 미친 할 수있는 것보다 당신은 선형 보간에 의해 수행
regions so yeah that's definitely something people are thinking about but
지역이 너무 좋아 그 확실히 사람들에 대해 생각하고 뭔가하지만,
it hasn't been incorporated into the into the whole pipeline yet
그것은 아직 전체 파이프 라인에 통합되지 않은
yeah
네
you could be slowed down your back in this sort of our CNN regime right and
당신이 우리의 CNN 정권 바로 이런 종류의에서 다시 둔화 될 수 있고,
look at that
저것 봐
250 times slower you really want to pay that price I mean I think another
250 시간은 느리게 당신은 정말 내가 다른 생각을 의미하는 가격을 지불 할 수
practical concern with rotated objects is that we don't really have that ground
회전 된 개체와 실제 관심은 우리가 정말 땅을하지 않아도됩니다
truth data sets so for most of these most of these detection dataset the only
진실 데이터가이 검출 데이터 세트의이 대부분의 대부분을 그렇게 설정 만
ground truth information we have are these access online bounding boxes so
지상 진실 정보 우리는 그래서 이러한 액세스 온라인 경계 상자입니다있다
it's hard you don't have a ground truth position that's kind of a practical
그것은 어려운 당신은 실제의 종류의 접지 진실 위치가 없습니다
concern I think people haven't really explored this so much so the end and
관심 나는 사람들이 정말 끝 그래서이 너무 많이 탐험하지 않은 생각
story with past our CNN has its super fast and it was about the same right
우리의 CNN은 슈퍼 빠른을 가지고 있으며,이 같은 오른쪽에 있었다 과거와 이야기
that's good and works actually really interesting is now at this point I knew
그 좋은 정말 재미있는 내가 아는이 시점에서 지금 실제로 작동
it you can actually understand the state of the art in object detection so this
당신은 실제로이 때문에 물체 검출에 예술의 상태를 이해할 수
is this is one of the best object detector in the world it crushed
이는 짓 눌린 세계 최고의 개체 검출기 중 하나입니다
everyone at the image that challenge in image and cocoa challenges in December
12 월 이미지와 코코아 도전에 도전 이미지에서 모두
and like most other thing is it's this deep residual network so the best object
대부분 같은 다른 것은 그것이 최고의 목적 때문에이 깊은 잔여 네트워크입니다입니다
in the world right now is a hundred and one layer residual network plus faster
세계에서 지금 백 하나의 층 잔여 네트워크는 빠른 플러스
our CNN plus a couple other goodies here right so we talked about we talk about
우리의 CNN 플러스 몇 가지 다른 케이크는 바로 여기 그래서 우리는 우리가 이야기에 대해 이야기
past our CNN we saw president last year they have to get an extra they always
그들은 항상 여분을 얻을 수있는 우리의 CNN 과거 우리가 작년에 대통령을 보았다
for competitions you need to add a couple of crazy things to get a little
대회를 위해 당신은 조금을 얻기 위해 미친 몇 가지를 추가해야
bit boost in performance right so here in this box refinements actually do
개선이 실제로 수행이 상자에 바로 그래서 여기에 성능이 약간 향상
multiple steps of refining the bounding box
바운딩 박스를 정제의 여러 단계
you saw that in the fast our CNN framework you doing this correction on
당신은 빠른 우리의 CNN 프레임 워크에이 보정에 일을 보았다
top of your region proposal could actually feed that back into the network
지역 제안 위에 실제로 네트워크로 그를 피드백 할 수
and reclassify Andrea get another production so that's this box refinement
즉,이 상자 정제 그래서 안드레아 다른 생산을 얻을 재 분류
step it gives you a little bit a boost they add context so in addition to
그것은 당신에게 후원을 조금주는 단계 그들은뿐만 아니라, 그래서 컨텍스트를 추가
classifying just just the region they get out of actor that gives you the
당신 제공 그들이 배우 나가 그냥 지역 분류
whole features for the entire image that sort of gives you more contacts than
종류의 당신에게보다 더 많은 접촉을 제공하는 전체 이미지에 대한 전체 기능
just that little crop net gives you a little bit more apartments and they also
그냥 작은 작물 그물 당신에게 조금 더 아파트 또한 제공
do multiscale testing kinda like we saw in over feet back so they actually run
우리는 그들이 실제로 실행할 수 있도록 다시 피트 이상에서 본 좀처럼 다중 스케일 테스트를 할
the thing on images at different size is a test time
다른 크기의 이미지에 대한 것은 시험 시간
an aggregate or those different sizes and when you put all those things
집계 또는 그 서로 다른 크기와 모든 것들을 넣을 때
together you win a lot of competitions so this thing one on SoCo actually
함께 실제로 SOCO에이 일 하나 때문에 대회를 많이 승리
Microsoft Coco actually runs a detection challenge and they wonder detection
마이크로 소프트 코코 실제로 검출 도전을 실행하고 검출 궁금해
challenge on cocoa we can also look at the rapid progress on the image that
우리는 또한 이미지에 급속한 진전을 볼 수 코코아에 도전하는
detection challenges over the last couple of years so you can see in 2013
지난 몇 년 동안 감지 도전은 그래서 당신은 2013 년에 볼 수 있습니다
was sort of the first time that we had these deep learning detection models so
우리가 이러한 깊은 학습 탐지 모델을 가지고 첫 번째 시간이었다 종류
over feat that we saw for localisation they actually submitted version of their
우리가 현지화 보았다 위업을 통해 그들은 실제로 버전을 제출 자신의
system that works on detection as well by sort of changing the logic with by
로와 로직을 변경의 종류에 의해뿐만 아니라 탐지 작동 시스템
which they merge bounding boxes and they did pretty good but they were actually
이들이 상자를 경계 병합 그들은 꽤 좋은했지만 그들은 실제로 있었다
outperformed by this other this other group called you vision that was sort of
이 다른이 다른 그룹보다 실적 일종의했다 당신의 비전을 호출
not a deep learning approach to use a lot of features but none in 2014 we
없는 깊은 학습 방법 2014 우리의 기능을 많이하지만 전혀 사용
actually saw both of these were deep learning approaches and Google actually
실제로 실제로 깊은 학습 방법과 구글이 모두 한보고
won that one by using a Google Map plus some other detection stuff on top of
하나 구글 맵 플러스의 상단에 다른 검출 재료를 사용하여 원
Google not and then in 2015 things went crazy and these residual networks plus
구글은하지 후 2015 일에 미친 이러한 잔류 네트워크 갔다 플러스
passer I CNN just crushed everything so I think that action especially over the
내가 통해 특히 해당 작업을 생각하도록 통행 나는 CNN은 모든 것을 분쇄
last couple years has been a really exciting thing because we've seen this
우리가 본 적이 있기 때문에 지난 몇 년은 정말 흥미 진진한 일이있다
really rapid progress over the last couple years in detection like most
가장 좋아 검출 지난 몇 년 동안 정말 빠른 진행
other things and another point I think it's kind of fun to make is that
다른 것들과 내가 생각하는 또 다른 포인트는 만드는 재미의 종류이다이다
actually for all I can to win competitions you know Andre said you
내가 할 수있는 모든 대회 우승을 위해 실제로는 앙드레 당신을 말했다 알고
ensemble and get 2% so you always win competitions with an ensemble but
앙상블과 항상 앙상블과 함께 경기를 승리 그래서 2 %를 얻을 수 있지만,
actually sort of fun microsoft also submitted their best single resident
실제로 종류의 재미 마이크로 소프트는 또한 최고의 단일 거주 제출
model this was not an ensemble and just a single resident model actually be all
이 앙상블이 아니었다 모델링하고 단 하나의 거주자 모델은 실제로 모든 일
the other things from all the other years that's actually pretty cool yeah
그래 정말 멋진 사실의 다른 모든 년에서 다른 것들
that's that's the best actor out there so this is kind of a funny thing right
즉,이 재미있는 일의 종류를 잘 그래서 그 밖에 최고의 배우입니다입니다
so this is a really so we we we talked about this idea of localisation as
그래서 이것은 정말 그래서 우리는 우리가 현지화의이 아이디어로 이야기 우리입니다
regression so this funny thing called Yolo you only look once actually tries
회귀 그래서 욜로 당신 만 보면이라는 재미있는 것은 한 번 실제로 시도
to oppose the detection problem directly as a regression problem so the idea is
아이디어 정도로 회귀 문제로 직접 검출 문제를 향하여
that we actually are going to take our input image and we're gonna divided into
우리는 실제로 우리의 입력 영상을하려고 우리는로 나누어거야 있음
some spatial grid they used to seven by seven and then within
일부 공간 격자 그들은 일곱하여 다음 내에서 칠하는 데 사용
each element about spatial grid we're gonna make six number of bounding box
공간 격자에 대한 각 요소는 우리가 거​​ 경계 상자의 여섯 번호를 확인하고
predictions they use be equal to I think in most of the experiments so then
예측은 내가 그렇게 한 다음 실험의 대부분의 생각에 동일하게 사용
within each grid you're going to predict maybe to be bounding boxes that's four
각 격자 내에는 네 어쩌면 경계 할 상자를 예측하는거야
numbers are also going to protect US single score for how much you believe
숫자는 미국 당신이 믿는 정도에 대한 하나의 점수를 보호하려고
that bounding box and you're also going to protect classification score for each
그 경계 상자는 당신은 또한 각 분류 점수를 보호하는거야
class near Davis at so then you can sort of take this this detection problem and
그래서 다음에 데이비스 근처 클래스는 정렬이이 검출 문제를 취할 수 있으며,
it ends up being regression your input is an image in your output is this maybe
그것은 회귀되는 것은 당신의 입력이 출력에 이미지가 어쩌면이입니다 끝
seven by seven by five B plus see answer right now just a regression problem and
오 B에 의해 일곱으로 칠 플러스 단지 회귀 문제를 지금 답변을보고
just try it and that's pretty cool and it's it's sort of a new approach to a
다만 그것을 시도하고 꽤 멋진 그리고 그것은에 새로운 접근 방식의 일종이다
bit different than these region proposal things that we've seen before
우리가 전에 본 적이 이러한 영역 제안 가지 다른 비트
of course sort of a problem with this is that there's an upper bound in the
물론 종류의이 문제는 바인드 상부있을 것입니다
number of outputs that your model can have so that might be a problem if
문제가있는 경우 일 수 있습니다 모델 그렇게 할 수 출력 수
you're testing data has many many more ground truth boxes in your training data
당신이 테스트하고 데이터는 훈련 데이터에 많은 더 많은 지상 진실 상자가
so this this yellow detector actually is really fast it's actually faster and
그래서이이 노란색 검출기는 실제로 빠른 실제로 빠르고입니다 정말
then faster our CNN which is pretty crazy but unfortunately it tends to work
다음 빠르게 꽤 미친 그러나 불행하게도 그것이 작동하는 경향이 우리의 CNN
a little bit worse so bad this other thing called fast yellow that i dont
조금 더 그렇게 나쁜 내가 그나마 빠른 노란색이라는 다른 것은
wanna talk about but
약 싶어 이야기하지만,
right but just as our number these are mean AP numbers on passed on one of the
중 하나에 전달 마우스 오른쪽 그러나 우리의 숫자로 이들은 평균 AP 번호는
Pascal data sets that we saw you can see yellow actually gets 64 that's pretty
파스칼 데이터는 우리가 당신이 볼 수 보았다 설​​정 노란색 실제로 64이 꽤있어 도착
good and runs at forty five frames per second that this is obviously on a
좋은이가에 분명히 초당 마흔다섯 프레임에서 실행
powerful GPU but still that's that's pretty much real time that's amazing
강력한 GPU는하지만 아직도 그게 놀라운 거의 실시간의의
was also I don't wanna talk about that right now knows these different versions
나는 싶어 지금이 다른 버전을 알고에 대해 얘기하지 마세요도했다
of past and Pastor are CNN's you can see that these actually pretty much all beat
과거와 목사의 CNN의 당신이 실제로 거의 모든 이길 것을 볼 수 있습니다
yo in terms of performance but are quite a bit slower yeah that's that's actually
성능면에서 요하지만 꽤 느린 그래 그 그 사실입니다입니다입니다
kind of a neat twist on the detection problem actually all these all these
검출 문제에 깔끔한 트위스트의 종류 실제로 모든 모든
different detection metric all these different detection models that we
다른 검출 메트릭이 모든 다른 검출 모델이 우리
talked about today they all pretty much have code up their released you should
오늘 이야기 그들은 모두 꽤 많이는 출시 당신이해야 코드를 가지고
maybe consider using them for projects probably don't use our CNN it's too slow
프로젝트는 아마 우리의 CNN을 사용하지 않는 어쩌면 너무 느린을 사용하는 것이 좋습니다
fast are seen on pretty good but requires MATLAB pastor our CNN there is
빠른 꽤 잘 볼하지만 우리의 CNN이 MATLAB 목사를 필요로하는
actually a Persian a pastor our CNN that doesn't require MATLAB is just Pipeline
실제로 페르시아는 MATLAB을 필요로하지 않는 목사 우리의 CNN은 파이프 라인이다
Cafe I haven't personally used it but it's something you might want to try to
카페 나는 개인적으로 그것을 사용하지 않은하지만 당신이 시도 할 수 있습니다 뭔가
use for your projects I'm not sure how difficult it is to get running and
프로젝트에 사용할 나는 그것이 실행 얻을 수 있습니다 얼마나 어려운지 잘 모르겠어요 및
yellow as actually I think maybe a good choice for some of your projects because
노란색 실제로 나는이 프로젝트 때문에 일부 아마 좋은 선택을 생각한다
it's so fast that it might be easier to work with if you have not be really big
당신이 정말 큰되지 않은 경우 작업을 쉽게 할 수 있도록 빨리
powerful GPUs and actually have caught up as well
실제로 강력한 GPU를하고도 잡았습니다
yes that's actually I got through things a little bit faster than expected so is
예 그게 내가 이렇게도 예상보다 조금 빨리 물건을 가지고 사실이다
there any questions on detection
검출에이 질문
yeah
네
yes in terms of model like model size it's pretty much about the same as a
예 모델의 크기와 같은 모델의 관점에서이 같은 대한 거의이다
classification model because when when you're running on bigger image
분류 모델을 사용하면 더 큰 이미지를 실행하는 경우 때 때문에
especially for faster our CNN right cause your convolutions you don't really
우리의 CNN이 바로 회선을 일으킬 특히 빠른 당신은 정말하지 않습니다
introduce any more parameters the full impact of layers are not really anymore
층의 전체 영향 아닌 정말 더 이상 더 이상 매개 변수를 소개합니다
parameters you have a couple extra parameters for the region proposal
당신은이 지역의 제안에 대한 몇 가지 추가 매개 변수가 매개 변수
network but it's basically the same number primaries as a classification
그러나 네트워크는 기본적으로 분류와 같은 다수의 원색
model right I guess I guess we're done a little early today
모델 바로 내가 오늘 일찍 우리가 조금 완료 추측 추측